<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Getting Started on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/index.html</link><description>Recent content in Getting Started on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 17:53:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The FHR Framework</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/the_phr_framework/index.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/the_phr_framework/index.html</guid><description>This section provides a conceptual overview of the ABDM federated health record framework. Read this to understand how various building blocks of ABDM works and where your application fits in this ecosystem.
Electronic Health Records Health Facility Registry (HFR) for facility identity What is a Health Information Provider (HIP)? What is a Health repository Provider (HRP)? Identifying patients via ABHA address Use ABHA number for patients without phones Health Information Exchange &amp;amp; Consent Manager Capturing ABHA address during patient registration Linking of records by HRP / HIP Discovery of records by patients Federated Health Records Architecture PHR applications &amp;amp; Health Lockers What are Health Information Users (HIUs) Sharing Health records with consent HIP / HIU Guidelines HDCM Policy ABDM uses a federated health record (FHR) framework that allows users (patients) to collect their health records across various healthcare providers, view their records from any Personal Health Record (PHR) application and share their records with their consent</description></item><item><title>About ABDM Sandbox</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/about_abdm_sandbox/index.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/about_abdm_sandbox/index.html</guid><description>The Ayushman Bharat Digital Mission (ABDM) has developed building blocks and APIs to offer a seamless digital healthcare experience for all stakeholders – health facilities, patients and healthcare workers. The digital infrastructure developed is now accessible to health facilities and health tech players for integration.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a picture to help you understand how ABDM can improve the experience you deliver to your patients :
ABDM Sandbox Journey ABDM aims at bringing out inoperability and sharing of health information among all the participants in India.</description></item><item><title>ABDM Sandbox Signup</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/abdm_sandbox_signup/index.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/abdm_sandbox_signup/index.html</guid><description>The ABDM sandbox is open to everyone including individuals. You use the sandbox environment to integrate your application and make sure it is compliant to the ABDM requirements. Access to ABDM production APIs requires you to exit the sandbox post integration.
User Manual for Sandbox Sign Up Step 1:
Start by registering yourself on ABDM Sandbox at the below URL . Refer here for signup details. https://sandbox.abdm.gov.in/applications/Home/signup_form
Step 2:
Your application will be reviewed by the Sandbox Committee.</description></item><item><title>Verify Sandbox Access</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/verify_sandbox_access/index.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/verify_sandbox_access/index.html</guid><description>Sign in to check application status Step 1: Once the Sandbox request form is submitted, the user can see the application submitted status by login in with Email id and Password.
https://sandbox.ndhm.gov.in/applications/Home/login
Step 2: On login, Application Submitted status (the current application status) is displayed in green.
For additional information on the various application status
Step 3: Once the application is Approved by the committee, the user will receive an email containing stating Client id &amp;amp; Client Secret.</description></item><item><title>Postman Setup</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/postman_setup/index.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/postman_setup/index.html</guid><description>Postman is one of the most popular software testing tools which is used for API testing. With the help of this tool, developers can easily create, test, share, and document APIs.
Overview Download And Install Postman Download Collections and Environment Variables Import Collections Import Environments Variables Verify Your Access To Sandbox Download And Install Postman App Steps to download and install the native Postman application
Step-1: Visit the https://www.postman.com/ website using any web browser and choose your desired platform among Mac, Windows or Linux.</description></item><item><title>Bahmni</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/bahmni/index.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/bahmni/index.html</guid><description>Bahmni Bahmni is an OpenMRS Distro. It is an open source EMR and a full Hospital Management System with Lab, Billing, Pharmacy, PACS and other integrated features. Bahmni functions as a Health Information Provider and Health Information User under the ABDM ecosystem.
Who is developing Bahmni? Thoughtworks started building Bahmni in January 2013 as part of its mission of social and economic justice. In October of 2017 Thoughtworks transferred ownership of Bahmni to the Bahmni Coalition under the Fiscal Sponsorship of the non-profit OpenMRS, Inc.</description></item><item><title>Sandbox ABHA App</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/sandbox_abha_app/index.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/sandbox_abha_app/index.html</guid><description>The ABDM Sandbox features a reference PHR application which can be used to simulate the consumer side experience. If the software you are integrating is a HMIS / LMIS, we highly recommend that you
Download and install the Sandbox ABHA app on an android phone Create an ABHA address that you will use during integration. This looks like yourid@sbx Setup a password for your ABHA address. This will be useful when we work with some APIs Download Sandbox ABHA App Sandbox ABHA App APK File</description></item><item><title>Working with ABDM APIs</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/working_with_abdm_apis/index.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/working_with_abdm_apis/index.html</guid><description>The Authorization Header Almost all ABDM APIs require you to pass the session token obtained via your client ID / secret in the Authorization HTTP Header. Remember to add the word &amp;ldquo;Bearer &amp;quot; in front of the JWT access Token you obtain from the https://dev.abdm.gov.in/gateway/v0.5/sessions
Authorization: Bearer eyJhbGciOiJSUzI1NiIsInR5cCIgOiAiSldUIiwia2lkIiA6IC..... ABDM Client IDs &amp;amp; Call Back URLs Every organization that registers with ABDM is issued one or more Client IDs Each Client ID should be used by the organization to register ONE INSTANCE of their ABDM compiliant software One Client ID can be used to register only ONE callback URL.</description></item><item><title>Encoding &amp; RSA Encryption</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/encoding-rsa-encryption/index.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/encoding-rsa-encryption/index.html</guid><description>Overview Convert Image to Base64 RSA Encryption Convert Image to Base64 Converting an image into Base64 string means taking the binary representation of an image and converting it into a string of ASCII digits (A-Z, a-z, 0-9).
To convert an image into Base64 :
use https://codebeautify.org/image-to-base64-converter After uploading the image and converting into Base64 string, copy the string and use it in the request body of API which expects it.</description></item><item><title>Become ABDM Compliant</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/making_your_app_abdm_compliant/index.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/making_your_app_abdm_compliant/index.html</guid><description>Making your App ABDM Compliant To become an ABDM Compliant Application, your application needs to implement specific functional capabilities and pass functional validation.
The functionality has been broken into milestones to make it easier to implement. Your first step is to understand the functionalities that your application must support. This depends on what type of application you are integrating.
Certification Functionality to be implemented M1 M2 M3 Locker Integrated Programs HFR HPR HMIS Applications - Used by Hospitals Yes Yes Yes NA NA Yes NA LMIS Application - Used by Labs Yes Yes NA NA NA Yes NA PHR Application - For consumers Yes Yes Yes Yes NA NA NA Public Health Application - Used by Health Workers Yes Yes Yes No Yes Yes NA Teleconsultation Application Yes Yes Yes No No Yes Yes Each functionality is defined by detailed test cases that must be passed to to obtain ABDM compliance.</description></item></channel></rss>