<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Getting Started on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</title>
    <link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Getting Started on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 17:53:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About ABDM Sandbox</title>
      <link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/about_abdm_sandbox/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/about_abdm_sandbox/index.html</guid>
      <description>ABDM Sandbox The Ayushman Bharat Digital Mission has developed building blocks and APIs to offer a seamless digital healthcare experience for all stakeholders – health facilities, patients and healthcare workers. The digital infrastructure developed is now accessible to health facilities and health tech players for integration.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a picture to help you understand different interaction touchpoints of a patient with the system:
ABDM Sandbox Journey ABDM aims at bringing out inoperability and sharing of health information among all the participants in India.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding the PHR Framework</title>
      <link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/understanding_the_phr_framework/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/understanding_the_phr_framework/index.html</guid>
      <description>ABDM uses a federated architecture to help users collect their health records across various healthcare providers, view their records from any PHR application and share their records with any requestor with their consent
The image below shows the various entities/roles involved in the PHR framework
What is a Health Information Provider (HIP)? Any entity that agrees to share digital health records with their users using the ABDM specified methods is called an HIP (Health Information Provider).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sign up to the ABDM Sandbox</title>
      <link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/sign_up_to_the_abdm_sandbox/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/sign_up_to_the_abdm_sandbox/index.html</guid>
      <description>Sign up for the ABDM Sandbox The building blocks of ABDM uses a JWT(JSON Web Token) token based auth mechanism for all API requests. Signing up to the ABDM sandbox provides you a client ID / client secret which can be used to generate the authorization token.
The ABDM sandbox is open to everyone including individuals. You use the sandbox environment to integrate your application and make sure it is compliant to the ABDM requirements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verify you can access the Sandbox</title>
      <link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/verify_you_can_access_the_sandbox/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/verify_you_can_access_the_sandbox/index.html</guid>
      <description>Signing in for the ABDM Sandbox Step 1: Once the Sandbox request form is submitted, the user can see the application submitted status by login in with Email id and Password.
https://sandbox.ndhm.gov.in/applications/Home/login
Step 2: On login, Application Submitted status (the current application status) is displayed in green.
Step 3: Once the application is Approved by the committee, the user will receive an email containing stating Client id &amp;amp; Client Secret. On Frontend, the user will see the status changed to Sandbox Application Status.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Working with ABDM APIs</title>
      <link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/working_with_abdm_apis/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/working_with_abdm_apis/index.html</guid>
      <description>How ABDM registers and identifies an entity Every organization that registers with ABDM is issued one or more Client IDs
Each Client ID should be used by the organization to register ONE INSTANCE of their ABDM compiliant software
Each instance of the software can hold health records for one or more health facilities
The figure below explains this using e-Hospital as an example
The Authorization Header Almost all ABDM APIs require you to pass the session token obtained via your client ID / secret in the Authorization HTTP Header.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making your App ABDM Compliant</title>
      <link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/making_your_app_abdm_compliant/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/making_your_app_abdm_compliant/index.html</guid>
      <description>The healthcare ecosystem has various types of applications. These include
HMIS / LMIS systems &amp;ndash; Anyone providing a healthcare software to hospitals, labs, clinics, etc Consumer Healthcare applications &amp;ndash; Personal Health record applications, Teleconsultation applications, etc. Anyone building healthcare applications for consumers / patients Government Health apps &amp;ndash; Software providers for goverment programs like RCH, NCD, NIKSHAY, COWIN, etc Each of the above apps can play multiple roles in the ABDM ecosystem depending on their requirement.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>