<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Milestone 3 on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/4-milestone3/index.html</link><description>Recent content in Milestone 3 on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 04:10:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/4-milestone3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Requesting Consent</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/4-milestone3/requesting-consent/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 04:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/4-milestone3/requesting-consent/index.html</guid><description>Requesting Consent Whoever wants to access health data, they have to request for user consent. They do this by sending a consent request with the user&amp;rsquo;s ABHA address to the HIE-CM
From an HIU perspective, the flow begins when the HIU (e.g. a Doctor at a Hospital) requests consent to view patient’s data.
Upon receipt of such a request from Gateway, CM acknowledges and sends back a consent request ID to the HIU via the gateway.</description></item><item><title>Storing Consent Artefacts</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/4-milestone3/storing-consent-artefact/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 04:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/4-milestone3/storing-consent-artefact/index.html</guid><description>Storing Consent Artefacts Patient Consent notification from CM to HIU Health Information Users (HIUs) need to be notified on the Users&amp;rsquo; consent, both when the user grants or revokes consent, or for an expired consent.
A consent can have different forms:
Grant Consent This is when the user grants consent to the HIU to access the health records or health information. Revoke Consent This is when the user revokes an earlier granted consent from the user, wherein they want to discontinue sharing their health records or heeath information.</description></item><item><title>Getting Health Records</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/4-milestone3/getting-health-record/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 04:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/4-milestone3/getting-health-record/index.html</guid><description>Getting Health Records The data request and transfer process between the HIU, CM and HIP passes through the following three stages:
First Stage
The HIU system initiates data request for a patient’s health information to the HIP against the relevant consent-artefact, through the CM. As part of the data request, the HIU’s health repository embeds three key elements within the health information request: The consent ID corresponding to the consent artefact against which the information request is being made.</description></item><item><title>Display Health Records</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/4-milestone3/display-health-record/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 04:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/4-milestone3/display-health-record/index.html</guid><description>Display Health Records For a given granted consent, the idea is to decrypt the received data and then display the health records in longitudinal format (that is, chronological order).
If the consent is revoked or expired then:
HIU should not display the health records of the user
HIU has to mandatorily delete any copy of health records that they hold
If there’s a way to summarise the results, analyse the reports so that it makes it easy for the Doctors / Consultants to make patient analysis easier.</description></item></channel></rss>