<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Milestone 2 on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/index.html</link><description>Recent content in Milestone 2 on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 04:10:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Health Record Formats</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/health-record-format/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 04:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/health-record-format/index.html</guid><description>Health Record Formats HRP can only link the following type of health records to an ABHA Address. All health records must be structured as FHIR (Fast Healthcare Interoperability Resources) formats. The FHIR specifications used by ABDM are published and maintained by the National Resource Centre for E-Health Standards (NRCES) at https://nrces.in/ndhm/fhir/r4/index.html.
All health records have been designed to be used in 2 ways
A simple FHIR bundle with a PDF or image attachment containing the detailed health information A structured FHIR bundle with coded health information.</description></item><item><title>Understanding Care Contexts</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/understand-care-context/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 04:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/understand-care-context/index.html</guid><description>Understanding Care Contexts A Care Context is a logical bundle of the health records. Each HMIS/LMIS system must decide how to organise data for a user into one or more care contexts. A care context is the element that is linked by the HMIS/LMIS with the ABHA address of the user. The HIE-CM is to be &amp;ldquo;data blind&amp;rdquo; by design, i.e. the HIE-CM should not have any visibility on the content of health records.</description></item><item><title>Link Care Context</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/link-care-context/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 04:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/link-care-context/index.html</guid><description>Link Care Context Linking of a care context can happen in 2 scenarios
Scenario 1:
User has shared ABHA Address during Registration HRP is expectated to initiate HIP initiated linking whenever a new health record is created for this user. It uses the linking token obtained and saved during registration to link a care context) Scenario 2:
User has not shared ABHA Address during Registration. HRP is expected to call a SMS notification API whenever a new health record is created for this user.</description></item><item><title>Understanding Consents</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/understanding-consents/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 05:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/understanding-consents/index.html</guid><description>Understanding Consents ABDM was designed to align with India&amp;rsquo;s Personal Data Protection Bill, that requires exchange of any personal data (like health data) to happen only with the consent of the User.
Any entity (Health Information User - HIU ) which would like to access health records that are linked to an ABHA address will require to first obtain a consent for data access.
The HIU needs to create a consent request that contains the following information:</description></item><item><title>Store Consent Artefacts</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/store-consent-artefacts/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 12:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/store-consent-artefacts/index.html</guid><description>Store Consent Artefacts All Health Information Providers (HIPs) who are holding any data associated with this consent are notified whenever a consent is granted, revoked, expired or the ABHA address is deleted.
THe HIP must save a copy of the consent artefact in their system. Data can be requested against a granted consent any number of times till the consent expires (or is revoked by the user).
When a user revokes a consent - the HIP must ensure that no further data is shared against this consent.</description></item><item><title>Request Health Records</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/request-health-records/index.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 05:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/request-health-records/index.html</guid><description>The data request and transfer process between the HIU, HIE-CM and HIP/HRP passes through the following three stages:
First Stage
The HIU system initiates a Health Information request (to the HIE-CM) for an ABHA address for which it has already been granted a consent.
The HIE-CM assigns a transaction ID for the entire data flow and communicates this Id to both the HIU and all the HRPs/ HIPs.
The HIU embeds three key elements within the health information request:</description></item><item><title>Packaging Health Data</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/packaging-health-data/index.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 05:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/packaging-health-data/index.html</guid><description>Packaging Health Data This section helps you understand data packaging, what goes into the main envelope, types of health information and much more. The examples provided in this section only explain the syntactic meaning of the data formats. For expressing symantec meaning via standards, encoding and terminologies please refer to the CDAC NRCeS website or as recommended by NHA.
Developers resource
You will need to use an FHIR client library to code the JSON samples provided in the sections below.</description></item><item><title>Encryption &amp; Decryption</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/encryption-decryption/index.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 05:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/encryption-decryption/index.html</guid><description>Encryption and Decryption The aim of encryption is to ensure that only the party (HIU) that has been granted consent by the user (or patient) is able to access the health data information of the user.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a high level overview on how the process of encyption and decryption works between HIUs and the HIPs, with the consent of the patient:
Every Health Information User (HIU) has 2 keys; that is public &amp;amp; private key.</description></item><item><title>Transferring Health Data</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/transfer-health-data/index.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 05:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/transfer-health-data/index.html</guid><description>Transferring Health Data Firewall Rules DataPush URL - can be any URL specified by the HIU. The HRP system must ensure that its firewall rules are setup in such a way that the outbound HTTPs requests can be to any URL
Security is ensured by making sure that the encrypted data can only be decrypted by requesting HIU
Posting the Data The encrypted data must be pushed to the HIU by the HRP within a short time frame.</description></item></channel></rss>