<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Milestone 2 on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/index.html</link><description>Recent content in Milestone 2 on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 04:10:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Health Record Formats</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/health-record-format/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 04:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/health-record-format/index.html</guid><description>Health Record Formats ABDM accepts only the documents that adhere to the FHIR&amp;rsquo;s (Fast Healthcare Interoperability Resources) Implementation Guidelines.
Here is a list of Health Records, based on FHIR&amp;rsquo;s specifications:
Name Definition Diagnostic Report Record The Clinical Artifact represents diagnostic reports including Radiology and Laboratory reports that can be shared across the health ecosystem. Discharge Summary Record Clinical document used to represent the discharge summary record for ABDM HDE data set.</description></item><item><title>Understand Care Context</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/understand-care-context/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 04:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/understand-care-context/index.html</guid><description>Understand Care Context The idea of Care Context is to create a logical bundle of the health records. Each HMIS/LMIS system must decide how they want to organise data in care context.
Our recommendations:
One care context for every outpatient visit &amp;amp; 1 care context for inpatient visit. Every care context has a reference ID, and a display name. The reference ID is internal to the hmis/lmis system &amp;amp; must be used to identify the set of health records associated with the care context.</description></item><item><title>Link Care Context</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/link-care-context/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 04:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/link-care-context/index.html</guid><description>Link Care Context This section covers: HIP Initiated linking Notification to Mobile Discovery &amp;amp; Link</description></item><item><title>Understanding Consents</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/understanding-consents/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 05:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/understanding-consents/index.html</guid><description>Understanding Consents ABDM design is aligned with India&amp;rsquo;s Personal Data Protection Bill, that is the exchange of health data can only happen with the consent of the User.
The entity requesting access to the data (HIU), needs to provide the following information:
The purpose for which they want access to data The historical time period of health data The type of health records How long they wish to keep a copy the data ABDM uses an electronic consent artefact based on MEITY&amp;rsquo;s electronic consent framework to allow HIUs to specify their consent request.</description></item></channel></rss>