<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ABDM Sandbox Documentation</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/</link><description>Recent content on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Choose the right integration</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/basics/integrators_overview/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/basics/integrators_overview/</guid><description>Signing up for the ABDM Sandbox Here is the process flow for the same
ABDM allows various types of entities to integrate with their APIs. Please choose the approprate type that fits your application from the choices below.
HMIS / LMIS systems &amp;ndash; Anyone providing a healthcare software to hospitals, labs, clinics, etc should start here Consumer Healthcare applications &amp;ndash; Personal Health record applications, Teleconsultations, etc. Anyone building healthcare applications for consumers / patients should start here Government Systems &amp;ndash; Any software provider for goverment programs like RCH, NCD, NIKSHAY, COWIN, etc should start here HMIS / LMIS Systems Please read the ABDM concepts overview first</description></item><item><title>Getting Started</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/basics/getting-started/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/basics/getting-started/</guid><description>Signing up for the ABDM Sandbox Here is the process flow for the same</description></item><item><title>Key Concepts for PHR</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/basics/abdm_concepts_overview/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/basics/abdm_concepts_overview/</guid><description>Signing up for the ABDM Sandbox Here is the process flow for the same
Overview of FHR framework Using the Federated Health Records framework (FHR), patients can access and view their health records, and provide consent to any HIPs and HIUs to access their data. This works in two ways:
Any HIU can request a patient’s information from an HIP, and obtain it through patient’s consent.
Any HIP can directly request the patient for consent to access their information.</description></item><item><title>Sign up to the ABDM Sandbox</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/basics/sandbox_signup_page/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/basics/sandbox_signup_page/</guid><description>Sign up for the ABDM Sandbox The building blocks of ABDM uses a JWT token based auth mechanism for all API requests. Signing up to the ABDM sandbox provides you a client ID / client secret which can be used to generate the authorization token.
The ABDM sandbox is open to everyone including induviduals. You use the sandbox environment to integrate your application and make sure it is compliant to the ABDM requirements.</description></item><item><title>Verify you can access the Sandbox</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/basics/sandbox_request_status_page/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/basics/sandbox_request_status_page/</guid><description>Signing up for the ABDM Sandbox Step 1: Once the Sandbox request form is submitted, the user can see the application submitted status by login in with Email id and Password.
https://sandbox.ndhm.gov.in/applications/Home/login
Step 2: On login, Application Submitted status in green color will be displayed and another status in Grey color.
Step 3: Once the application is Approved by the committee, an email will be received by the user stating Client id &amp;amp; Client Secret.</description></item><item><title/><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/basics/integrators_section/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/basics/integrators_section/</guid><description>ABDM allows various types of entities to integrate with their APIs. Please choose the approprate type that fits your application from the choices below.
Please read the ABDM Concepts Overview first
HIMS / LIMS Systems Entities providing a healthcare software to hospitals, labs, clinics, etc comes under this category.
HIMS Maintain, collect and manage health records. Ensure timely and accurate delivery of data to health care providers. In return the health care providers rely on the information to deliver quality healthcare</description></item></channel></rss>