<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ABDM Sandbox Home on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/index.html</link><description>Recent content in ABDM Sandbox Home on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 17:53:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Getting Started</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/index.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 17:53:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/index.html</guid><description>Getting Started with ABDM This section covers Understanding the ABDM Personal Health Records (PHR) Framework Learn the ABDM terminology - HIP / HIU / HPR / PHR / Locker Apply for access to the Sandbox &amp;amp; verify your credentials Understand what integration is required to make your application ABDM compliant Setup POSTMAN and get started using ABDM APIs Setup a Sandbox ABHA Address for use during testing Setup an end point URL for your health repository or consumer health application Link health facilities with your health repository Stakeholders in ABDM Patients ADBM will enable patients to be able to register rapidy during their health visit, collect their health records across any health facility, book appointments with doctors and share their health information with consent.</description></item><item><title>Milestone 1</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/index.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 04:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/index.html</guid><description>Milestone 1 (M1) Functionalities to be implemented as part of Milestone 1 are:
Create ABHA number - using Aadhaar / Mobile / Demographic / Driving License Collect &amp;amp; Verify ABHA address during patient registration M1 Test Cases mapping by Role Applicable To HMIS / LMIS (PVT) Govt. Health App Creation of ABHA Number Using Aadhar OTP Mandatory Mandatory Using Aadhar Biometrics Optional Mandatory Using Aadhar Demographics (Offline) NA Mandatory Using Driving License Optional Optional Download ABHA Card Mandatory Mandatory Default ABHA Address NA NA Profile Update Optional Optional Verification of ABHA Address Scan Health Facility QR Mandatory Mandatory Scan User ABHA QR Mandatory Mandatory By OTP Mandatory Mandatory New vs Returning Patients Mandatory Mandatory This section covers: Creation of ABHA number Using Aadhaar OTP Using Aadhaar biometric Using Aadhaar demographics (offline) Using driving license Download ABHA Card Default ABHA Address Profile Update Verification of ABHA address By scan &amp;amp; share By OTP By demographics New vs Returning Patients</description></item><item><title>Milestone 2</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 04:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/index.html</guid><description>Get Milestone 2 Certified Functionalities of Milestone 2: Building Health Information Provider (HIP) services to share digital records via any Personal Health Records (PHR) application.
The Milestone 2 can be explained with 2 scenarios:
Scenario 1:
User has shared ABHA Address during Registration (1 of 3 ways from verification of ABHA address) Expectation is HIP initiated linking (that whenever a new health record is created for this user, it is linked to a care context) Scenario 2:</description></item><item><title>Milestone 3</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/4-milestone3/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 04:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/4-milestone3/index.html</guid><description>Get Milestone 3 Certified Functionalities of Milestone 3: Developing Health Information User (HIU) services to provide view of patient’s medical history to authorized healthcare workers with complete consent.
Milestone 3 revolves around HIUs, here&amp;rsquo;s a quick snapshot to understand what functionalities will be covered in this section:
M3 Test Cases mapping by Role Applicable To HMIS / LMIS (PVT) Govt. Health App Requesting Consent Mandatory Mandatory Storing Consent Artefacts Mandatory Mandatory Getting Health Records Mandatory Mandatory Display Health Records Mandatory Mandatory This section covers: Requesting Consent Storing Consent Artefacts Getting Health Records Display Health Records</description></item><item><title>Building a PHR App</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/5-building-a-phr-app/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 05:53:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/5-building-a-phr-app/index.html</guid><description>Building a PHR Application Important to understand:
All the APIs here are synchronous The interaction is between PHR Application &amp;amp; HIE-CM The PHR Application has 2 components:
PHR App UI PHR App Cloud Here&amp;rsquo;s a diagram to understand the functionalities of the 2 components:
This section covers:
Create ABHA Address Using Mobile number Using ABHA number Ling / De-link of ABHA address &amp;amp; ABHA number Login &amp;amp; Manage User Profile Setting up subscription Setting up Auto-Approval Handling notifications Discovery &amp;amp; Linking of records Supporting UHI: intent Fetching &amp;amp; Display of Records Managing Consents / Subscription Requests: Listing Consents / Subscription requests Granting Consents / Subscription requests Revoking Consents / Subscription requests Uploading User Record Sharing your PHR address at a Health facility Link/Unlink PHR Address to an ABHA number</description></item><item><title>Health Facility Registry</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-hfr/index.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 07:53:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-hfr/index.html</guid><description>Health Facility Registry Health Facility Registry is a comprehensive repository of health facilities of the country across modern and traditional systems of medicine.
It includes both public and private health facilities including hospitals, clinics, diagnostic laboratories and imaging centers, pharmacies, etc.
ABDM maintains the national directory of all Healthcare Facilities. A facility needs to first enrol in the health facility registry.
Benefits of Health Facility Registry :
Unique &amp;amp; Trustable Identity Facility ID for identification of health facilities across the ABDM ecosystem.</description></item><item><title>Health Professional Registry</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/7-hpr/index.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 07:53:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/7-hpr/index.html</guid><description>Healthcare Professional Registry Healthcare Professionals Registry is a comprehensive repository of all verified healthcare professionals involved in delivery of healthcare services across both modern and traditional systems of medicine. Enrolling in the Healthcare Professionals Registry will enable them to get connected to India’s digital health ecosystem.
Currently Doctors and Nurses can enroll in HPR and going forward other categories of professionals will be added.
User manual
HPR user manual Download here API documents</description></item><item><title>UHI</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/8-uhi/index.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 07:53:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/8-uhi/index.html</guid><description>UHI &amp;amp; UHI Network UHI is envisioned as an open protocol for various digital health services. UHI Network will be an open network of End User Applications (EUAs) and participating Health Service Provider (HSP) applications.
UHI will enable a wide variety of digital health services between patients and health service providers (HSPs) including, but not limited to:
Booking OPD appointments at hospitals / clinics Booking Tele-Consultation Discovering availability of critical care beds Discovery of lab and diagnostic services Booking of home visits for lab sample collections Booking an ambulance Discovery of nearby pharmacies End user application (EUA) is any application chosen by the service consumer (frequently referred to as user) to access Health services.</description></item><item><title>HCX Integrators</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/9-hcx-integrators/index.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 07:53:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/9-hcx-integrators/index.html</guid><description>HCX Integrators Please visit HCX Documentation for detailed Health Claims Exchange Specifications.
To support the vision of Pradhan Mantri Jan Arogya Yojana (PMJAY), NHA has created a standardized health claim platform based on the Health Claim Exchange Specification (HCX) to enable automation of the health claim-related information exchange between payers, providers, beneficiaries, and other relevant entities.
The specification provides an interoperable, machine-readable, auditable, verifiable, and open standard-based structure protocol for communication between the entities.</description></item><item><title>Test Cases</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/10-test-cases/index.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 17:53:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/10-test-cases/index.html</guid><description>Test Cases This section covers:
Milestone 1 Test Cases Milestone 2 Test Cases Milestone 3 Test Cases PHR Application Test Cases</description></item><item><title>Swagger</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/11-swagger/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 17:53:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/11-swagger/index.html</guid><description>Swagger This section covers: Complete Swagger For ABHA Number APIs V1/V2 V3 HIP APIs HIU APIs PHR APIs ABHA Address APIs HIE-CM APIs</description></item><item><title>9-health-facility-registries</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/9-health-facility-registry/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/9-health-facility-registry/index.html</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>