<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ABDM Sandbox Home on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/</link><description>Recent content in ABDM Sandbox Home on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 17:53:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ABHA ID Registration via Aadhaar</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/abha-id-registration/registration-via-aadhaar/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/abha-id-registration/registration-via-aadhaar/</guid><description>Overview of the functionality User can register ABHA ID with their Aadhaar Number. To enable beneficiary registration using Aadhaar OTP, an integrator needs to generate an Aadhaar OTP, followed by OTP verification. Once the OTP is verified, the client is returned complete profile data along with ABHA (Health ID) Number. Note: Mobile Number can be linked/verify with ABHA via using API
Registration via Aadhaar Number API Sequence The sequence of APIs used via this method are shown in the diagram below.</description></item><item><title>By scanning HIP QR code</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/scanning-hip-qr/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/scanning-hip-qr/</guid><description>Overview of the functionality Patient must have a PHR app and have a valid PHR address Hospital must generate a HIP QR code and display it at the registration counter Patient scans the QR code from his phone camera or his PHR app If scanned from phone camera &amp;ndash; The list of installed PHR apps is shown on the phone. The user can select any of the apps if scanned from within the PHR app, the app will call the share-profile API on the HIE-CM The HIE-CM will verify this is a registered healthcare provider and call the share-profile api on the end of the HRP that is linked to this HIP The HRP software can create a screen to display all the scanned profiles and allow the operator to select them for fast registration include any images from the PHR app / EMRSBX for this feature</description></item><item><title>By scanning HIP QR code</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/shared-verbally/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/shared-verbally/</guid><description>Overview of the functionality Patient must have a valid PHR address Patient verbally shares the PHR address at the Health operator. OTP authentication will be required only if PHR address is shared verbally. include any images from the PHR app / EMRSBX for this feature
API Sequence S.No Collection &amp;amp; verification of ABHA by HIP APIs call on the Gateway APIs that are expected to be available at the HIP end by the Gateway 1.</description></item><item><title>ABHA ID Registration via Other Documents</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/abha-id-registration/registration-via-other-documents/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/abha-id-registration/registration-via-other-documents/</guid><description>Registration via Other Documents Overview of the functionality Currently we support Driving License (DL) &amp;amp; PAN for ABHA number generation, apart from Aadhaar.
ABDM plans to roll out other ID documents as well to enable creation.
The same will be communicated and updated in the documentation as necessary.
However, the integration flow will remain as the DL/PAN flow.
To enable beneficiary registration using other documents, the user is requested his/her mobile number to be linked with ABHA (Health ID) Number.</description></item><item><title>By scanning PHR Address QR</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/scanning-phraddr-qr/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/scanning-phraddr-qr/</guid><description>Overview of the functionality Patient must have a PHR app or PHR card and have a valid PHR address Hospital must have a scanner available at the registration counter Hospital operator scans the QR code on patient PHR card or from PHR mobile App. After scanned HIP will call the share-profile API on the HIE-CM The HIE-CM will verify this is a registered healthcare provider and call the share-profile api on the end of the HRP that is linked to this HIP The HRP software can create a screen to display all the scanned profiles and allow the operator to select them for fast registration Then the detials like ABHA ID, PHR address,name,gender,sateId,districtId,dob,address will be shared with health facility API Sequence API Information Request Response Get patient&amp;rsquo;s Details URL: https://dev.</description></item><item><title>Understanding the PHR Framework</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/phr_architecture_overview/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/phr_architecture_overview/</guid><description>ABDM uses a federated architecture to help users collect their health records across various healthcare providers, view their records from any PHR application and share their records with any requestor with their consent
The image below shows the various entities involved in the PHR framework
What is an Health Information Provider (HIP)? Any entity that agrees to share digital health records with their users using the ABDM specified methods is called an HIP (Health Information Provider).</description></item><item><title>Link/De-link of ABHA Address</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/abha-id-registration/link-delink-abha-addr/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/abha-id-registration/link-delink-abha-addr/</guid><description>Link/De-link of ABHA Address Overview of the functionality ABDM has now segregated the identity layer from the consent layer, which will ensure that the ABHA Number (earlier known as Health ID) provides a strong identity to an individual whereas an ABHA Address (earlier known as PHR Address) enables an individual to share their health records with different healthcare providers and payers. ABHA number can be link/delink with the ABHA address.</description></item><item><title>Sign up to the ABDM Sandbox</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/sandbox_signup_page/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/sandbox_signup_page/</guid><description>Sign up for the ABDM Sandbox The building blocks of ABDM uses a JWT token based auth mechanism for all API requests. Signing up to the ABDM sandbox provides you a client ID / client secret which can be used to generate the authorization token.
The ABDM sandbox is open to everyone including induviduals. You use the sandbox environment to integrate your application and make sure it is compliant to the ABDM requirements.</description></item><item><title>Discovery from PHR Apps</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/discovery-from-phrapp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/discovery-from-phrapp/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Verify you can access the Sandbox</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/sandbox_request_status_page/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/sandbox_request_status_page/</guid><description>Signing up for the ABDM Sandbox Step 1: Once the Sandbox request form is submitted, the user can see the application submitted status by login in with Email id and Password.
https://sandbox.ndhm.gov.in/applications/Home/login
Step 2: On login, Application Submitted status in green color will be displayed and another status in Grey color.
Step 3: Once the application is Approved by the committee, an email will be received by the user stating Client id &amp;amp; Client Secret.</description></item><item><title>Choose the right integration</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/integrators_overview/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/integrators_overview/</guid><description>What are you trying to integrate? Various types of entities can integrate with the ABDM building blocks via APIs. These include
HMIS / LMIS systems &amp;ndash; Anyone providing a healthcare software to hospitals, labs, clinics, etc Consumer Healthcare applications &amp;ndash; Personal Health record applications, Teleconsultations, etc. Anyone building healthcare applications for consumers / patients Government Systems &amp;ndash; Any software provider for goverment programs like RCH, NCD, NIKSHAY, COWIN, etc It is recommended that you read the (ABDM PHR concepts)[/abdm-docs/basics/abdm_concepts_overview/] overview first before getting into futher details of how to integrate.</description></item><item><title/><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/integrators_section/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/integrators_section/</guid><description>ABDM allows various types of entities to integrate with their APIs. Please choose the approprate type that fits your application from the choices below.
Please read the ABDM Concepts Overview first
HIMS / LIMS Systems Entities providing a healthcare software to hospitals, labs, clinics, etc comes under this category.
HIMS Maintain, collect and manage health records. Ensure timely and accurate delivery of data to health care providers. In return the health care providers rely on the information to deliver quality healthcare</description></item></channel></rss>