<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ABDM Sandbox Home on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/</link><description>Recent content in ABDM Sandbox Home on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 17:53:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ABHA ID Registration via Aadhaar</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/abha-id-registration/registration-via-aadhaar/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/abha-id-registration/registration-via-aadhaar/</guid><description>Overview of the functionality User can register ABHA ID with their Aadhaar Number. To enable beneficiary registration using Aadhaar OTP, an integrator needs to generate an Aadhaar OTP, followed by OTP verification. Once the OTP is verified, the client is returned complete profile data along with ABHA (Health ID) Number. Note: Mobile Number can be linked/verify with ABHA via using API
Registration via Aadhaar Number API Sequence The sequence of APIs used via this method are shown in the diagram below.</description></item><item><title>By scanning HIP QR code</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/scanning-hip-qr/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/scanning-hip-qr/</guid><description>Overview of the functionality Patient must have a PHR app and have a valid PHR address Hospital must generate a HIP QR code and display it at the registration counter Patient scans the QR code from his phone camera or his PHR app If scanned from phone camera &amp;ndash; The list of installed PHR apps is shown on the phone. The user can select any of the apps if scanned from within the PHR app, the app will call the share-profile API on the HIE-CM The HIE-CM will verify this is a registered healthcare provider and call the share-profile api on the end of the HRP that is linked to this HIP The HRP software can create a screen to display all the scanned profiles and allow the operator to select them for fast registration !</description></item><item><title>Deactivate via Aadhaar Otp</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/deactivate-abha/delete-via-aadhaar-otp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/deactivate-abha/delete-via-aadhaar-otp/</guid><description>Deactivate ABHA via Aadhaar Otp Overview of the functionality Users may De-activate his/her ABHA (Health ID) Following will happen (during the deactivation period) if you deactivate your ABHA (Health ID) :
You will lose access to all ABDM applications. You will no longer be able to share your health records over the ABDM network. You will no longer be able to share your ABHA (Health ID) at any health facility.</description></item><item><title>Deactivate via Mobile Otp</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/deactivate-abha/deactivate-via-mobile-otp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/deactivate-abha/deactivate-via-mobile-otp/</guid><description>Deactivate ABHA via Mobile Otp Overview of the functionality Users may De-activate his/her ABHA (Health ID) Following will happen (during the deactivation period) if you deactivate your ABHA (Health ID) :
You will lose access to all ABDM applications. You will no longer be able to share your health records over the ABDM network. You will no longer be able to share your ABHA (Health ID) at any health facility.</description></item><item><title>Delete via Aadhaar Otp</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/delete-abha/delete-via-aadhaar-otp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/delete-abha/delete-via-aadhaar-otp/</guid><description>Delete ABHA via Aadhaar Otp Overview of the functionality Users may delete his/her ABHA (Health ID) permanently. Following will happen if you delete your ABHA (Health ID) :
Your ABHA (Health ID) will be permanently deleted, along with all your demographic details . You will not be able to retrieve any information tagged to your ABHA (Health ID) in future. You will never be able to access ABDM applications or any health records over the ABDM network with your deleted ABHA (Health ID).</description></item><item><title>Delete via Mobile Otp</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/delete-abha/delete-via-mobile-otp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/delete-abha/delete-via-mobile-otp/</guid><description>Delete ABHA via Mobile Otp Overview of the functionality Users may delete his/her ABHA (Health ID) permanently. Following will happen if you delete your ABHA (Health ID) :
Your ABHA (Health ID) will be permanently deleted, along with all your demographic details . You will not be able to retrieve any information tagged to your ABHA (Health ID) in future. You will never be able to access ABDM applications or any health records over the ABDM network with your deleted ABHA (Health ID).</description></item><item><title>Get User profile</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/user-profile/get-profile/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/user-profile/get-profile/</guid><description>Get User profile Overview of the functionality Get the User profile API Sequence API Information Request Response Api gets the user account information.
URL: https://healthidsbx.ndhm.gov.in/api/v1/account/profile
Request: GET
Parameters:
Authorization string (header)
X-HIP-ID string (header)
X-Token string (header)
Body:
{ } Response: 200 OK
{ &amp;#34;address&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;string&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;authMethods&amp;#34;: [ &amp;#34;AADHAAR_OTP&amp;#34; ], &amp;#34;dayOfBirth&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;string&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;districtCode&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;string&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;districtName&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;string&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;email&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;string&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;firstName&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;string&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;gender&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;string&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;healthId&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;string&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;healthIdNumber&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;string&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;kycPhoto&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;string&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;lastName&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;string&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;middleName&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;string&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;mobile&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;string&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;monthOfBirth&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;string&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;name&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;string&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;new&amp;#34;: true, &amp;#34;pincode&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;string&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;profilePhoto&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;string&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;stateCode&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;string&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;stateName&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;string&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;subDistrictCode&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;string&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;subdistrictName&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;string&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;tags&amp;#34;: { &amp;#34;additionalProp1&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;string&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;additionalProp2&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;string&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;additionalProp3&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;string&amp;#34; }, &amp;#34;townCode&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;string&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;townName&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;string&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;villageCode&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;string&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;villageName&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;string&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;wardCode&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;string&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;wardName&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;string&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;yearOfBirth&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;string&amp;#34; } Postman + Curl Collection Download the Postman Collection here</description></item><item><title>Login with Aadhaar OTP</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/login-abha-id/login-with-aadhaar-otp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/login-abha-id/login-with-aadhaar-otp/</guid><description>Login with Aadhaar OTP Overview of the functionality An OTP is triggered with the Aadhaar linked mobile number of the patient. The patient must provide the OTP to the user to complete the authentication API Sequence The sequence of APIs used via this method are shown in the diagram below.
API Information Request Response Authentication token public certificate. This certificate is also used to encrypt the data. URL: https://healthidsbx.</description></item><item><title>Reactivate via Aadhaar OTP or Mobile OTP</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/reactivate-abha/reactivate-abha/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/reactivate-abha/reactivate-abha/</guid><description>Reactivate via Aadhaar OTP or Mobile OTP Overview of the functionality Users may Reactivate his/her ABHA (Health ID) via Aadhaar OTP or Mobile OTP by using the below endpoints. API Sequence API Information Request Response Initiate authentication for reactivation of Health ID URL: https://healthidsbx.ndhm.gov.in/api/v2/auth/reactivate/init
Request: POST
Parameters:
Authorization string (header)
X-HIP-ID string (header)
Body:
authRequest (body)
{ &amp;#34;authMethod&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;AADHAAR_OTP&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;healthid&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;43-4221-5105-6749&amp;#34; } Response: 200 OK</description></item><item><title>Retrieve ABHA via Aadhaar OTP</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/retrieve-abha-account/retrieve-abha-aadhaar-otp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/retrieve-abha-account/retrieve-abha-aadhaar-otp/</guid><description>Retrieve ABHA via Aadhaar OTP Overview of the functionality To retrieve ABHA (Health ID), an OTP is sent on a registered mobile number and the user&amp;rsquo;s health ID is retrieved from the ABDM server. The sequence of APIs used via this method is shown in the diagram below. API Sequence The sequence of APIs used via this method are shown in the diagram below.
API Information Request Response Generate Aadhaar OTP on Registered mobile number Explanation - API accepts Aadhaar Number and then generates OTP for linked number as part of Forgot flow.</description></item><item><title>ABHA ID Registration via Other Documents</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/abha-id-registration/registration-via-other-documents/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/abha-id-registration/registration-via-other-documents/</guid><description>ABHA ID Registration via Other Documents Overview of the functionality Currently we support Driving License (DL) &amp;amp; PAN for ABHA number generation, apart from Aadhaar.
ABDM plans to roll out other ID documents as well to enable creation.
The same will be communicated and updated in the documentation as necessary.
However, the integration flow will remain as the DL/PAN flow.
To enable beneficiary registration using other documents, the user is requested his/her mobile number to be linked with ABHA (Health ID) Number.</description></item><item><title>By scanning PHR Address QR</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/scanning-phraddr-qr/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/scanning-phraddr-qr/</guid><description>Overview of the functionality Patient must have a PHR app or PHR physical card and have a valid PHR address Hospital must have a 2D Barcode scanner available at the registration counter Hospital operator scans the QR code on patient PHR card or from PHR mobile App The Patient details like ABHA ID, ABHA address, Name, Gender, State Id, District Id, DOB, State Name, District Name, Mobile and Address are encoded in the QR Code After scanning the QR Code the details of the patient are shared in JSON format { &amp;#34;hidn&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;12-3456-7777-7777&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;hid&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;test@ndhm&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;name&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;gender&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;statelgd&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;7&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;distlgd&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;77&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;dob&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;1977&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;state name&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;DELHI&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;district_name&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;CENTRAL&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;mobile&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;+919999977777&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;address&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;&amp;#34; } The HRP software registration page have text box to load data scanned from PHR QR Code.</description></item><item><title>Get User QR Code</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/user-profile/get-qr-code/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/user-profile/get-qr-code/</guid><description>Get User QR Code Overview of the functionality Get the User QR code API Sequence API Information Request Response Get Quick Response code in PNG format for this account
URL: https://healthidsbx.ndhm.gov.in/api/v1/account/qrCode
Request: GET
Parameters:
Authorization string (header)
X-HIP-ID string (header)
X-Token string (header)
Body:
{ } Response: 200 OK
{ string } Postman + Curl Collection Download the Postman Collection here</description></item><item><title>Login with Mobile OTP</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/login-abha-id/login-with-mobile-otp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/login-abha-id/login-with-mobile-otp/</guid><description>Login with Mobile OTP Overview of the functionality An OTP is sent to the patient’s mobile number that is linked with the Health ID. The patient must share the OTP with the user for verification. A token has been returned and can be used for Profile APIs purpose. API Sequence The sequence of APIs used via this method are shown in the diagram below.
API Information Request Response Authentication token public certificate.</description></item><item><title>Retrieve ABHA via Mobile OTP</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/retrieve-abha-account/retrieve-abha-mobile-otp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/retrieve-abha-account/retrieve-abha-mobile-otp/</guid><description>Retrieve ABHA via Mobile OTP Overview of the functionality To retrieve ABHA (Health ID), an OTP is sent on mobile number along with the user&amp;rsquo;s demographic detail. User&amp;rsquo;s health ID is retrieved from the ABDM server. API Sequence The sequence of APIs used via this method are shown in the diagram below.
API Information Request Response Api Accepts Mobile Number and then generates OTP for it to Start Registration URL: https://healthidsbx.</description></item><item><title>Understanding the PHR Framework</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/phr_architecture_overview/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/phr_architecture_overview/</guid><description>ABDM uses a federated architecture to help users collect their health records across various healthcare providers, view their records from any PHR application and share their records with any requestor with their consent
The image below shows the various entities involved in the PHR framework
What is an Health Information Provider (HIP)? Any entity that agrees to share digital health records with their users using the ABDM specified methods is called an HIP (Health Information Provider).</description></item><item><title>By sharing PHR verbally</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/shared-verbally/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/shared-verbally/</guid><description>Overview of the functionality Patient must have a valid PHR address Patient verbally shares the PHR address at the Health operator. OTP authentication will be required only if PHR address is shared verbally. include any images from the PHR app / EMRSBX for this feature
API Sequence S.No Collection &amp;amp; verification of ABHA by HIP APIs call on the Gateway APIs that are expected to be available at the HIP end by the Gateway 1.</description></item><item><title>Link/De-link of ABHA Address</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/abha-id-registration/link-delink-abha-addr/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/abha-id-registration/link-delink-abha-addr/</guid><description>Link/De-link of ABHA Address Overview of the functionality ABDM has now segregated the identity layer from the consent layer, which will ensure that the ABHA Number (earlier known as Health ID) provides a strong identity to an individual whereas an ABHA Address (earlier known as PHR Address) enables an individual to share their health records with different healthcare providers and payers. ABHA number can be link/delink with the ABHA address.</description></item><item><title>Login to your ABHA using Mobile</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/login-abha-id/login-using-mobile/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/login-abha-id/login-using-mobile/</guid><description>Login to your ABHA using Mobile Overview of the functionality Users will now be able to login to their ABHA using their Mobile Number. In case multiple ABHA numbers are linked to a Mobile Number, users will be able to choose the account they want to login to. The patient must provide the OTP to the user to complete the authentication. To begin the process, the Authentication token public certificate API (V1.</description></item><item><title>Sign up to the ABDM Sandbox</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/sandbox_signup_page/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/sandbox_signup_page/</guid><description>Sign up for the ABDM Sandbox The building blocks of ABDM uses a JWT token based auth mechanism for all API requests. Signing up to the ABDM sandbox provides you a client ID / client secret which can be used to generate the authorization token.
The ABDM sandbox is open to everyone including induviduals. You use the sandbox environment to integrate your application and make sure it is compliant to the ABDM requirements.</description></item><item><title>Update Email</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/user-profile/update-email/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/user-profile/update-email/</guid><description>Update User E-mail Overview of the functionality OTP will be sent to the provided e-mail address. OTP will be valid for 10 minute only. To Update or Changes the existing e-mail Address (Verified/Unverified email). Send the New Email Address required in the request. API Sequence API Information Request Response To generate the Email Verification OTP to verify the Email Address in the profile. OTP will be sent to the provided email address.</description></item><item><title>Discovery from PHR Apps</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/discovery-from-phrapp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/discovery-from-phrapp/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Update Mobile via Aadhaar Otp</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/user-profile/update-mobile-via-aadhaar-otp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/user-profile/update-mobile-via-aadhaar-otp/</guid><description>Update Mobile via Aadhaar Otp Overview of the functionality To update the mobile using Aadhaar OTP , a client ( Integrator) needs to first generate Mobile OTP and verify it. Again generate Aadhaar OTP and a transaction ID is returned. Auth token, OTP, old password along with transaction ID is passed in the requested body and client is returned with the status of changed mobile number. API Sequence The sequence of APIs used via this method is shown in the diagram below.</description></item><item><title>Update Mobile via Mobile Otp</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/user-profile/update-mobile-via-mobile-otp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/user-profile/update-mobile-via-mobile-otp/</guid><description>Update Mobile via Mobile Otp Overview of the functionality To update the mobile using Mobile OTP , a client ( Integrator) needs to first generate Mobile OTP on a new number and verify it. Again generate Aadhaar OTP on the old number and a transaction ID is returned. Auth token, OTP , along with transaction ID is passed in the requested body and the client is returned with the status of changed mobile number.</description></item><item><title>Verify you can access the Sandbox</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/sandbox_request_status_page/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/sandbox_request_status_page/</guid><description>Signing up for the ABDM Sandbox Step 1: Once the Sandbox request form is submitted, the user can see the application submitted status by login in with Email id and Password.
https://sandbox.ndhm.gov.in/applications/Home/login
Step 2: On login, Application Submitted status in green color will be displayed and another status in Grey color.
Step 3: Once the application is Approved by the committee, an email will be received by the user stating Client id &amp;amp; Client Secret.</description></item><item><title>Choose the right integration</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/integrators_overview/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/integrators_overview/</guid><description>What are you trying to integrate? Various types of entities can integrate with the ABDM building blocks via APIs. These include
HMIS / LMIS systems &amp;ndash; Anyone providing a healthcare software to hospitals, labs, clinics, etc Consumer Healthcare applications &amp;ndash; Personal Health record applications, Teleconsultations, etc. Anyone building healthcare applications for consumers / patients Government Systems &amp;ndash; Any software provider for goverment programs like RCH, NCD, NIKSHAY, COWIN, etc It is recommended that you read the (ABDM PHR concepts)[/abdm-docs/basics/abdm_concepts_overview/] overview first before getting into futher details of how to integrate.</description></item><item><title/><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/integrators_section/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/1-basics/integrators_section/</guid><description>ABDM allows various types of entities to integrate with their APIs. Please choose the approprate type that fits your application from the choices below.
Please read the ABDM Concepts Overview first
HIMS / LIMS Systems Entities providing a healthcare software to hospitals, labs, clinics, etc comes under this category.
HIMS Maintain, collect and manage health records. Ensure timely and accurate delivery of data to health care providers. In return the health care providers rely on the information to deliver quality healthcare</description></item></channel></rss>