<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Verification of ABHA Address on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/verify-abha-address/index.html</link><description>Recent content in Verification of ABHA Address on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 17:53:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/verify-abha-address/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Scan Health Facility QR</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/verify-abha-address/health-facility-qr-scan/index.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 09:30:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/verify-abha-address/health-facility-qr-scan/index.html</guid><description>Scan Health Facility QR Functionality Overview Patients can scan a Health Facility QR code pasted at the facility registration counter on their ABHA application.
The User/Patient can share their basic KYC information with the Health Facility (HMIS/LIMS) by scanning the QR Code using the ABHA application. This enables the user/patients to complete the seamless profile share during their visit.
Steps to scanning the QR Code: Patient must have an ABHA app and have a valid ABHA address Hospital must generate a Health Facility QR code and display it at the registration counter Patient can then scan the QR code from his phone camera or his ABHA application If scanned from phone camera &amp;ndash; The list of installed PHR apps is shown on the phone.</description></item><item><title>Scan User ABHA QR</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/verify-abha-address/user-abha-qr-scan/index.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 09:30:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/verify-abha-address/user-abha-qr-scan/index.html</guid><description>Scan User ABHA QR Functionality Overview Health Facility can scan the User&amp;rsquo;s ABHA QR code, whereby User provides consent to link the Health Record to their account.
Health Facility (HIP) Initiated linking is the process through which an HIP links the patient’s care context (health record) with the patient ABHA Address, after patient registration and creation of health records (in their HMIS/LMIS system).
Sample QR Codes QR Code JSON output Sample QR Code in User&amp;rsquo;s ABHA Application Sample QR Code in User&amp;rsquo;s ABHA Card Care context (Health record) linking happens in two steps:</description></item><item><title>By OTP</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/verify-abha-address/by-otp/index.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 09:30:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/verify-abha-address/by-otp/index.html</guid><description>By OTP</description></item><item><title>By Demographic</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/verify-abha-address/demographic/index.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 09:30:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/verify-abha-address/demographic/index.html</guid><description>By Demographic</description></item></channel></rss>