<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Building UHI Apps on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</title>
    <link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Building UHI Apps on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 17:53:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>UHI Protocol</title>
      <link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/about_uhi/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/about_uhi/index.html</guid>
      <description>What is UHI? The Unified Health Interface (UHI) is a network where applications built on the UHI open protocol can interoperably connect with each other to provide health services. UHI is a key Digital Public Infrastructure that enables discoverability and transaction for digital health services. UHI works with other ABDM building blocks like HIE-CM for interoperable exchange of personal health data and registries like HPR &amp;amp; HFR to enable trust from participating doctors and health facilities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UHI Architecture Overview</title>
      <link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/uhi_architecture_overview/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/uhi_architecture_overview/index.html</guid>
      <description>UHI Architecture UHI aims to transform the way digital health services are rendered in India, while ensuring that it is in sync with the other building blocks of ABDM. The functional architecture for UHI is mentioned below. The aim of this architecture is to ensure interoperability for health services and health data. The architecture also depicts how UHI will interact with the other building blocks within ABDM.
Architecture Steps 1.A Patient Sign Up/ Login: Patients login using their ABHA number/ Aadhar number / Mobile Number.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Registrating your UHI app</title>
      <link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/uhi_sandbox_registry/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/uhi_sandbox_registry/index.html</guid>
      <description>The UHI Registry Before your EUA or HSPA app can talk to other UHI apps, you must first add it into the UHI registry.
Go to the Sandbox webpage at https://sandbox.abdm.gov.in/
If you have already signed up for the Sandbox use the link for existing ABDM partners https://sandbox.abdm.gov.in/applications/Home/signup_form_UHI
If you are new to the ABDM sandbox, ensure you select if you want to build an UHI EUA or UHI HSPA or both.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sandbox Gateway, EUA &amp; HSPA</title>
      <link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/uhi_sandbox_gw/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/uhi_sandbox_gw/index.html</guid>
      <description>The UHI Gateway on Sandbox ABDM is operating a UHI gateway as part of its sandbox. This gateway can be used by UHI app developers to build and test their apps.
Every Application accessing the gateway must first register itself in the UHI registry on Sandbox. The UHI gateway does not have any web interface. It merely responds to the search / on_search request from UHI applications.
Sandbox UHI Gateway URL https://uhigatewaysandbox.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building UHI EUA App</title>
      <link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-eua/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 17:53:25 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-eua/index.html</guid>
      <description>This details out the steps to build your own EUA app including
Sign up / Sign in with PHR Address Select a UHI service Teleconsultations Search HSPAs for Doctor Display search results Book selected Doctor/Facility Collect Payment if required Confirm Booking Exchange Messages with Doctor Share health records Setup WebRTC (teleconsults) Initiate Call (teleconsults) Get final prescription Appointment booking Search HSPAs for Facility/Doctor Display search results Book selected Facility/Doctor Collect Payment if required Confirm Booking Ambulance booking Search HSPAs for Facility/Doctor Display search results Book selected Facility/Doctor Collect Payment if required Confirm Booking </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building UHI HSPA App</title>
      <link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-hspa/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 17:53:25 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-hspa/index.html</guid>
      <description>This details out the steps to build your own HSPA app including
Sign up / Sign in with HPR ID Setup for Teleconsults Setup for Physical Appointments See list of Appointments Initiate Teleconsultation Share OPD Notes / Prescription View Settlements </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>