<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Building UHI HSPA App on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-hspa/</link><description>Recent content in Building UHI HSPA App on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 17:53:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-hspa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sign In or Sign UP with HPR ID</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-hspa/sign-up-or-sign-in-with-hpr-id/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-hspa/sign-up-or-sign-in-with-hpr-id/</guid><description>The HSPA allows Health Service Providers (HSP) - at present limited to doctors - to provide healthcare services through UHI to patients. The HSP can Sign In with the HP ID linked mobile number if available, alternatively they can sign up to register themselves on HPR.
The sign in process requires API calls to the Health Professionals Registry (HPR) which is a database for health professionals.
UI Reference [Sign In Reference Screens].</description></item><item><title/><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-hspa/see-list-of-appointment-and-initiate-consultation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-hspa/see-list-of-appointment-and-initiate-consultation/</guid><description>See list of Appointments and Initiate Consultation The doctor can see their list of upcoming appointments by navigating through the homepage of the HSPA. While seeing their appointments, they are provided with a functionality to initiate a call to the patient.
UI Reference API Documentation to be added</description></item><item><title/><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-hspa/setup-for-physical-consultation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-hspa/setup-for-physical-consultation/</guid><description>Setup for Physical Consultation The setup for physical appointments is similar to setting up a teleconsultation service except the doctor doesn&amp;rsquo;t need to provide their signature for signing the prescriptions.
Set up Calendar/availability Provide their fees/charges Provide bank details/UPI address to receive payments UI Reference API Documentation to be added</description></item><item><title/><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-hspa/setup-for-teleconsultation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-hspa/setup-for-teleconsultation/</guid><description>Setup for Teleconsultation A doctor, after signing in, can select the services they want to provide through the HSPA. There are 3 major steps that a doctor needs to complete before providing any service through UHI
Set up calendar/availability Provide their fees/charges for the service Provide their UPI address/ Bank details and upload a signature for e-signing the prescriptions UI Reference API Documentation to be added</description></item><item><title/><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-hspa/share-opd-notes-or-prescription/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-hspa/share-opd-notes-or-prescription/</guid><description>Share OPD Notes or Prescription After the teleconsultation has been completed with a patient, the doctor can share the prescription with the patient. The prescription format in the reference app compiles with the telemedicine guidelines.
UI References API Documentation to be added</description></item><item><title/><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-hspa/view-settlements/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-hspa/view-settlements/</guid><description>View Settlements The doctors can see the payment/settlement made against a service provided by navigating from the home screen and seeing their account statement in the app.
UI Reference API Documentation to be added</description></item></channel></rss>