<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Creation of ABHA Number on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</title>
    <link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/abha-number/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Creation of ABHA Number on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 17:53:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/abha-number/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Using Aadhaar OTP</title>
      <link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/abha-number/aadhar-otp/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 09:30:25 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/abha-number/aadhar-otp/index.html</guid>
      <description>Registration via Aadhaar OTP Functionality Overview ABHA Number can be obtained via self-registration using Aadhaar as KYC with valid user consent where user is giving his consent to create ABHA number. ABHA enrolment using Aadhaar has strong KYC validation. Once user is successfully authenticated, the system will generate 14 digit ABHA number
Following are the steps to successfully integrate the ABHA registration via Aadhaar:
The User should input the Aadhaar number as an input.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Aadhar Biometric</title>
      <link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/abha-number/aadhar-biometric/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 09:30:25 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/abha-number/aadhar-biometric/index.html</guid>
      <description>Coming Soon.. Overview To enable beneficiary registration using Aadhaar Biometric, a client needs to have a Aadhaar Registered Device (RD Device) that allows capture and processing of Biometrics of the beneficiary. This RD Service returns an encrypted PID block containing signed biometrics (using device private key within the registered devices secure zone) back to the calling application. To enable beneficiary registration using biometrics, this PID is passed in the request along with Aadhaar and other required details.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Aadhar Demographic</title>
      <link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/abha-number/aadhar-demographic/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 09:30:25 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/abha-number/aadhar-demographic/index.html</guid>
      <description>Using Aadhar Demographic </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Driving License</title>
      <link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/abha-number/driving-license/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 09:30:25 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/abha-number/driving-license/index.html</guid>
      <description>ABHA ID Registration via Driving Licence Overview of the functionality Currently ABDM support Driving License (DL) for ABHA number generation, apart from Aadhaar.
To enable beneficiary registration using other documents, the user is requested his/her mobile number to be linked with ABHA Number.
An OTP is sent to the given mobile number and after verifying the OTP , demographic information of the user is captured along with the driving license number .</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>