<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Login with ABHA (Health ID) on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/7-m1-apis/login-abha-id/index.html</link><description>Recent content in Login with ABHA (Health ID) on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 17:53:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/7-m1-apis/login-abha-id/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Login with Aadhaar OTP</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/7-m1-apis/login-abha-id/login-with-aadhaar-otp/index.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/7-m1-apis/login-abha-id/login-with-aadhaar-otp/index.html</guid><description>Login with Aadhaar OTP Overview of the functionality An OTP is triggered with the Aadhaar linked mobile number of the patient. The patient must provide the OTP to the user to complete the authentication API Sequence The sequence of APIs used via this method are shown in the diagram below.
API Information Request Response 1. Generate the Gateway session
Bearer token is received as part of respose and should be passed a Authorization token for subsequent API calls.</description></item><item><title>Login with Mobile OTP</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/7-m1-apis/login-abha-id/login-with-mobile-otp/index.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/7-m1-apis/login-abha-id/login-with-mobile-otp/index.html</guid><description>Login with Mobile OTP Overview of the functionality An OTP is sent to the patient’s mobile number that is linked with the Health ID. The patient must share the OTP with the user for verification. A token has been returned and can be used for Profile APIs purpose. API Sequence The sequence of APIs used via this method are shown in the diagram below.
API Information Request Response 1. Generate the Gateway session</description></item><item><title>Login to your ABHA using Mobile</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/7-m1-apis/login-abha-id/login-using-mobile/index.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/7-m1-apis/login-abha-id/login-using-mobile/index.html</guid><description>Login to your ABHA using Mobile Overview of the functionality Users will now be able to login to their ABHA using their Mobile Number. In case multiple ABHA numbers are linked to a Mobile Number, users will be able to choose the account they want to login to. The patient must provide the OTP to the user to complete the authentication. To begin the process, the Authentication token public certificate API (V1.</description></item></channel></rss>