<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Building a PHR App on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/4-building-a-phr-app/</link><description>Recent content in Building a PHR App on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 17:53:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/4-building-a-phr-app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sign Up or Sign in</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/4-building-a-phr-app/signup-or-signin/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/4-building-a-phr-app/signup-or-signin/</guid><description>Sign up / Sign in Every PHR App user needs to have an ABHA Address (also reffered to as PHR Address). The address looks like &amp;ldquo;username@hie-cm&amp;rdquo;. Currently ABDM manages 2 HIE-CMs. The Sandbox HIE-CM @sbx and the production HIE-CM @abdm. PHR Apps use APIs provided by the HIE-CM to create a new ABHA address for users.
The user chosen ABHA address has to be alphanumeric. The only numeric address allowed is 14 digits and that must be a valid ABHA number.</description></item><item><title/><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/4-building-a-phr-app/edit-your-phr-profile/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/4-building-a-phr-app/edit-your-phr-profile/</guid><description>Edit your profile User can view and edit his/her profile in the View complete Profile on dashboard. The screen displays QR code which user can use to share the information with HIP and can also download the ABHA card. The screen also displays user details that are KYC verified (Aadhar verified profile) and cannot be edited such as
Name Gender DOB Other details displayed are editable such as Mobile Email ID Address District State Pin Code In self-verified profile (Created by Mobile/Email ID), all the details can be edited.</description></item><item><title/><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/4-building-a-phr-app/link-unlink-abha-number/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/4-building-a-phr-app/link-unlink-abha-number/</guid><description>ABHA number is the uniquely generated 14 digit number which provides the strong identity to an individual, whereas ABHA address is use to share the health records of the individual with different healthcare providers and payers. Individual can link/Unlink ABHA number with the ABHA address to experience the benefits of both.
Link ABHA number In link ABHA number flow, the ABHA address is linked with the ABHA number of the user.</description></item><item><title/><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/4-building-a-phr-app/sharing-your-phr-address-at-a-health-facility/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/4-building-a-phr-app/sharing-your-phr-address-at-a-health-facility/</guid><description>Sharing your PHR address at a Health facility User can share his/her profile using QR code scanner which is on the top right side of the screen. When clicked, it opens the new screen where details of user is displayed such as
Name ABHA address Year of Birth Gender User has also being provided with the option to share QR Code. User can also download and view his/her ABHA address card.</description></item></channel></rss>