<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Building a PHR App on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/4-building-a-phr-app/</link><description>Recent content in Building a PHR App on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 17:53:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/4-building-a-phr-app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sign Up or Sign in using PHR Addr</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/4-building-a-phr-app/signup-or-signin/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/4-building-a-phr-app/signup-or-signin/</guid><description>Sign up or Sign in using PHR Address Sign up/Registration in PHR App The PHR mobile application developed by ABDM is now known as ABHA mobile application and has been taken as a reference PHR application. In this application, by registration, we mean creating an ABHA address aka PHR address, which is an easy-to-remember address.
ABHA address has to be alphanumeric. The only numeric address allowed is 14 digits and that must be a valid ABHA number.</description></item><item><title/><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/4-building-a-phr-app/link-unlink-abha-number/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/4-building-a-phr-app/link-unlink-abha-number/</guid><description>ABHA number is the uniquely generated 14 digit number which provides the strong identity to an individual, whereas ABHA address is use to share the health records of the individual with different healthcare providers and payers. Individual can link/Unlink ABHA number with the ABHA address to experience the benefits of both.
Link ABHA number In link ABHA number flow, the ABHA address is linked with the ABHA number of the user.</description></item></channel></rss>