<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Teleconsultations on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-eua/teleconsults/</link><description>Recent content in Teleconsultations on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 17:53:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-eua/teleconsults/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Search HSPAs for Doctor</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-eua/teleconsults/search_hspas_for_doctor/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-eua/teleconsults/search_hspas_for_doctor/</guid><description>The user can search for a doctor using one or multiple criteria. The supported criteria include
Doctor name/HPID Specialities System of medicine City Hospital/facility Availability Type of consultation A search can also be completed by a patient browsing their appointment history The EUA fires Search API onto the HSPAs to look for the doctors matching the search criteria across the network. UI Reference API Sequence Example JSONs The following JSONs represent the Search API that are fired from the EUA for each of the above criteria.</description></item><item><title>Display Search Results</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-eua/teleconsults/display_search_results/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-eua/teleconsults/display_search_results/</guid><description>Display search results The HSPAs respond with on_search API to send back the HPID of the doctors who match the search criteria of EUA. The EUA looks up the Health Professionals Registry (HPR) to fetch the details of the doctor against the HPIDs received from the HSPA. The other details such as the quote and availability are fetched by the EUA from the HSPA directly by firing the search API again to the HSPA with the specific doctor’s HPID.</description></item><item><title>Book Selected Doctor</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-eua/teleconsults/book-selected-doctor-or-facility/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-eua/teleconsults/book-selected-doctor-or-facility/</guid><description>Book selected Doctor/Facility User selects the time and date for the service for the selected doctor from the available appointment calendar. User initiates the booking. Init API call is made to the HSPA with the above details and receives the revised quote and payment terms from the HSPA. UI Reference ![Book Selected Doctor or Facility]../(Book_Selected_UIR.png)
API Sequence ![Book Selected Doctor or Facility]../(Book_Selected_SeqAPI.png)
Example JSONs The /init API is fired to the HSPA with the selected date and time as well as the customer and billing details.</description></item><item><title>Collect Payment</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-eua/teleconsults/collect-payment-if-required/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-eua/teleconsults/collect-payment-if-required/</guid><description>Collect Payment if Required The HSPA responds to the request by the EUA through on_init API. The HSPA sends the revised quote for the service booking and additionally sends terms of payment for the service. Depending on the payment terms the next step could lead to the EUA redirecting the user towards a payment gateway. UI Reference</description></item><item><title>Confirm Booking</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-eua/teleconsults/confirm-booking/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-eua/teleconsults/confirm-booking/</guid><description>Confirm Booking Upon successful collection of payment or acceptance of agreeing to pay as per the terms sent by the HSPA the EUA calls the /confirm API on the HSPA. The HSPA responds with an on_confirm API to confirm the booking of the service and sends confirmation of the appointment with the doctor along with all the details of the appointment such as the doctor details, slot, payment, billing etc. UI Reference API Sequence Example JSONs The /init API is fired to the HSPA with the selected date and time as well as the customer and billing details.</description></item><item><title>Exchange Messages with Doctor</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-eua/teleconsults/exchange-messages-with-doctor/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-eua/teleconsults/exchange-messages-with-doctor/</guid><description>Exchange Messages with Doctor The exchange message functionality will be enabled as soon as the appointment with the doctor is confirmed by the HSPA. This will allow asynchronous messaging between the patient and the doctor.
UI Reference</description></item><item><title>Share Health Record</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-eua/teleconsults/share-health-records/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-eua/teleconsults/share-health-records/</guid><description>Share Health Records The shared health records functionality allows the patient to share health records linked to their ABHA address with the doctor. The reference EUA at present, provides a non-native experience to the patient, where, upon confirmation of appointment, health record sharing request is auto-triggered by the HSPA. The patient can choose any PHR application to share their health records with the doctor.
The functionality will be updated to provide a native experience to the user and the documentation will be updated accordingly.</description></item><item><title>Setup Video Call</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-eua/teleconsults/setup-webrtc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-eua/teleconsults/setup-webrtc/</guid><description>Setup WebRTC The EUA and HSPA provide real time communication between the patient and doctor using the WebRTC protocol.
To be added</description></item><item><title>Initiate Call</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-eua/teleconsults/initiate-call-tele-consults/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-eua/teleconsults/initiate-call-tele-consults/</guid><description>Initiate Call (Teleconsultation) The functionality to initiate a call with the doctor is enabled 30 mins prior to the scheduled appointment. The user starts the consultation only when the doctor allows them to join until then the user waits in the digital waiting room.
Reference UI</description></item><item><title>Get Final Prescription</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-eua/teleconsults/get-final-prescription/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/uhi/building-uhi-eua/teleconsults/get-final-prescription/</guid><description>Get final prescription The prescription sent by the doctor to the patient gets linked to their ABHA address. The user needs to be notified to check the PHR app to approve addition of the prescription to their health records.
Note: Current reference EUA provides a non-native (patient moves out of the EUA) experience to the patient for addition of health records. This documentation will be updated as the functionality moves to a native experience for the user.</description></item></channel></rss>