<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Building a PHR App on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/5-building-a-phr-app/index.html</link><description>Recent content in Building a PHR App on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 05:53:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/5-building-a-phr-app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Creation of ABHA Address</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/5-building-a-phr-app/create-abha-address/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 05:53:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/5-building-a-phr-app/create-abha-address/index.html</guid><description>Creation of ABHA Address Understanding ABHA Address What is ABHA Address?
ABHA Address is an easy to remember username that enables a user to access their health records digitally and share their records with various healthcare providers. An ABHA address may look like ‘name@abdm’. It is required to sign up on ABHA Application
Every 14-digit ABHA number is automatically issued a default ABHA address on the ABDM HIE-CM, which looks like 14-digit@sbx or 14-digit@abdm.</description></item><item><title>Login to PHR App</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/5-building-a-phr-app/login-user/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 05:53:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/5-building-a-phr-app/login-user/index.html</guid><description>Login to PHR App Functionality Overview PHR App should allow the user to log in to the PHR application with any of the Auth methods.
It can also save the refresh token and extend the user session to reduce the number of times the user has to keep logging in.
A single PHR app can manage multiple user profiles by offering a sign in-sign out
More information: Every PHR Applicationi user needs to have an ABHA Address (also reffered to as PHR Address).</description></item><item><title>Manage User Profile</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/5-building-a-phr-app/manage-user/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 05:53:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/5-building-a-phr-app/manage-user/index.html</guid><description>Manage PHR App User&amp;rsquo;s Profile Functionality Overview PHR applications need to have a (this) section, where users can view their demographic details and update (edit) their information.
The section should also display ABHA QR code as part of the Profile information
They should also be able to set/change password from this section.
Similarly, they should also have an option to set/change consent pin.
The user should also be able to upload a profile photo from this section.</description></item><item><title>Scan &amp; Share</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/5-building-a-phr-app/scan-share/index.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 03:53:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/5-building-a-phr-app/scan-share/index.html</guid><description>Scan and Share Functionality Overview Every PHR Application needs to provide the ability for their users to scan a health facility QR code and share their ABHA address, profile information with health facilities.
The App must be able to integrate with the phone camera and read the content of QR Code The App must also support an intent where it must go directly to the sharing page, if the QR code was scanned with a different camera.</description></item><item><title>Setup &amp; Manage Subscriptions</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/5-building-a-phr-app/setup-subscriptions/index.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 05:53:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/5-building-a-phr-app/setup-subscriptions/index.html</guid><description>Setting up &amp;amp; Managing Subscriptions Functionality Overview In ABDM, any HIU or PHR Application can subscribe (that is help you to watch for changes to PHR address) for notifications to be received on its callback URL whenever there is a change in the care context linked to a ABHA Address.
Every PHR App must set up a subscription for the ABHA address:
When it creates ABHA address User logs in with a new ABHA address PHR applications are expected to provide a UI layer where the user can: View the list of subscriptions Approve subscriptions Deny subscriptions The PHR app is responsible for showing up notifications on the Mobile application (for example using Firebase in Android).</description></item><item><title>Handling Notifications</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/5-building-a-phr-app/handling-notifications/index.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 03:53:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/5-building-a-phr-app/handling-notifications/index.html</guid><description>Handling Notifications Functionality Overview A PHR Application handles a variety of notifications for the User.
Types on notifications to be handled:
Care context - new/updated New subscription request (v3 APIs only) New Consent request (v3 APIs only) Approved / Revoked consents Expectation on Care Context - new/updated
This happens if a subscription is set up for this ABHA address. whenever there is a new care context linked or updated. The PHR App must notify the user on the UI that there is a new health record available.</description></item><item><title>Setup Auto-Approval</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/5-building-a-phr-app/setup-auto-approval/index.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 03:53:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/5-building-a-phr-app/setup-auto-approval/index.html</guid><description>Setting up Auto-Approval Functionality Overview The PHR App should get confirmation from the user that it can automatically retrieve any new linked health records and save a copy in the PHR application. On confirmation from the user, the PHR app can set up an auto-approval policy with the HIE-CM. The HIE-CM responds with an auto-approval ID that must be saved by the PHR app. When the PHR App receives a notification for a new care context or update of a care context, it is expected to initiate a consent request to the HIE-CM for access to the linked care context Since the auto approval policy is in place the HIE-CM will immediately respond with a consent grant to the PHR app.</description></item><item><title>Discovery &amp; Linking Records</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/5-building-a-phr-app/discovery-linking-records/index.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 03:53:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/5-building-a-phr-app/discovery-linking-records/index.html</guid><description>Discovery and Linking of Records Functionality Overview This is applicable when the user has not shared ABHA address when they visit a Health facility. This can also be used by users to discover and link historical records from health facility. How to do this:
User should be able to search the Healthcare provider (health facility) by name in the PHR application The Discovery and Link feature can also be used to find &amp;amp; link records held by large govt.</description></item><item><title>Support Deep links</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/5-building-a-phr-app/support-deep-links/index.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 03:53:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/5-building-a-phr-app/support-deep-links/index.html</guid><description>Support Deep Links Functionality Overview Any mobile application that can display a user&amp;rsquo;s personal health record (ABHA) under the Ayushman Bharat Digital Mission (ABDM) needs to adhere to the deep linking specification outlined in this document.
User Flow:
Patient visits a health facility and registers by providing Name, DoB, Gender and Mobile. Patient does not share any ABHA Address with the facility. If the Health Facility is participating in ABDM, then it will notify ABDM when there is a new health record for this patient.</description></item><item><title>Fetch &amp; Display Records</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/5-building-a-phr-app/fetch-display-records/index.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 03:53:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/5-building-a-phr-app/fetch-display-records/index.html</guid><description>Fetching and Display of Records Functionality Overview Every PHR Application also needs to implement an HIU (Health Information User) The process for implementing HIU is described in Milestone 3. Whenever a new care context is linked to the ABHA address, the PHR App receives a notification. The PHR app is expected to create a consent request for that health record and send it to the HIE-CM. If auto-approval policy is in place, the consent is immediately approved.</description></item><item><title>Managing Consents</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/5-building-a-phr-app/managing-consents/index.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 03:53:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/5-building-a-phr-app/managing-consents/index.html</guid><description>Managing Consents Functionality Overview The role of the PHR app is to help the user to manage the consent request. The PHR App must:
List all of the consent requests that have been sent to the user
Allow the User to edit the content of the consent request and modify it as per their requirements.
Allow the user to grant / deny a new consent request.
Allow the users to view granted consents and revoke them at any point in time.</description></item><item><title>Uploading User Record</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/5-building-a-phr-app/upload-user-records/index.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 03:53:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/5-building-a-phr-app/upload-user-records/index.html</guid><description>Uploading User Record Functionality Overview PHR Applications must allow users to scan and upload any records that they may have with them. This includes: physical records, output from IoT devices like BP meter, Glucose meters; and health devices like fit-bit, smartwatches etc The PHR application can decide the HI type of the record based on the contents or user input. If the HI type cannot be determined the PHR app is expected to use HI type as “HealthDocumentRecord”.</description></item></channel></rss>