<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Link Care Context on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/link-care-context/index.html</link><description>Recent content in Link Care Context on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 04:10:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/link-care-context/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HIP Initiated linking</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/link-care-context/hip-initiated-linking/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 04:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/link-care-context/hip-initiated-linking/index.html</guid><description>HIP Initiated linking This is applicable when User has shared an ABHA address during registration.
Whenever a new health record is created for a patient, decide which care context this will be a part of.
The HRP must link the care context as soon as the health record is ready to be shared with the user
Linking the care context requires a linking token. This is obtained and saved at the time of registration.</description></item><item><title>Notification to Mobile</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/link-care-context/notification-mobile/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 04:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/link-care-context/notification-mobile/index.html</guid><description>Notification to Mobile Applicable when: User does not share ABHA address during registration but shares mobile, name, age, gender.
Health Information Provider (HIP) must call an ABDM API when a new health record is ready to be shared with an user. ABDM sends the SMS to notify the user that they can access and link the new health record using any PHR app. The SMS contains a deep link the triggers the PHR app.</description></item><item><title>Discovery &amp; link</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/link-care-context/discovery-link/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 04:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/link-care-context/discovery-link/index.html</guid><description>Discovery and Linking of patient records ABDM allows a user to find their health records from any health facility they have visited via the discovery process. Users can use an PHR app to select the health facility they visited and initiate a &amp;ldquo;Discovery&amp;rdquo; request The HIE-CM forwards the discovery request to the the HRP linked to the health facility All HRPs / HIPs must correctly implement the discovery API The HRP is expected to return all the care contexts for the user if records are found The user can then link them to their ABHA address.</description></item></channel></rss>