<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Packaging Health Data on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/packaging-health-data/index.html</link><description>Recent content in Packaging Health Data on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 05:10:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/packaging-health-data/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Main Envelope</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/packaging-health-data/main-envelope/index.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 05:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/packaging-health-data/main-envelope/index.html</guid><description>Main Envelope The base FHR envelope contains all the data that you want to transfer, compiled as a FHIR Bundle. A FHIR Bundle, referred to as data content, allows for packaging information of multiple types or as a Document.
You can send over multiple such bundles through the data transfer API. Note that the bundle itself must be encrypted. Note: Refer to the API reference documentation for information on bundles and how data should be sent over HTTPs.</description></item><item><title>Diagnostic Reports</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/packaging-health-data/diagnostic-reports/index.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 05:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/packaging-health-data/diagnostic-reports/index.html</guid><description>Diagnostic Reports as FHIR DiagnosticReport You may send more structured information for a Diagnostic Report (advised), by using the FHIR DiagnosticReport resource. Typically the most important elements of DiagnosticReports are:
code: The examples given below show only textual element &amp;rsquo;text&amp;rsquo;, but you may use &amp;lsquo;Coding&amp;rsquo; along with &amp;lsquo;display&amp;rsquo; element expressing a human readable name. issued: Date and time when the report was issued, usually after the report was reviewed and verified.</description></item><item><title>Encryption and Decryption</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/packaging-health-data/encryption-decryption/index.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 05:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/packaging-health-data/encryption-decryption/index.html</guid><description>Data Encryption and Decryption The following abbreviations are used in this section:
ECDH: Elliptic-curve Diffie–Hellman Key Exchange AES-GCM: Advanced Encryption Standard-Galois/Counter Mode DHPK: Elliptic-curve Diffie–Hellman public key DHSK: Elliptic-curve Diffie–Hellman secret/private key P and U is annotation for system DHK(U,P): Elliptic-curve Diffie–Hellman Key Rand: Random String Information shared as part of the data flow will be secured using an encryption mechanism that ensures perfect forward secrecy. This means that even if any of the key materials stored at HIPs, HIUs or HDCM clients (either long-term private keys or session keys) are compromised, it would not be possible to decipher data that was previously exchanged.</description></item><item><title>Testing Health Repositories</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/packaging-health-data/testing/index.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 05:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/packaging-health-data/testing/index.html</guid><description>How to test the Health Repositories Please note: UI mockups in section are for illustrative purposes only and meant to provide general guidelines. Actual UI on application might be different or more refined.
HIU doctors can view patient&amp;rsquo;s health data only when your system is integrated with the health repository. To check if your HIP bridge is built properly and can be linked by a user, perform the following tasks:</description></item></channel></rss>