<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Collect PHR Address on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/</link><description>Recent content in Collect PHR Address on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 17:53:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>By scanning HIP QR code</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/scanning-hip-qr/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/scanning-hip-qr/</guid><description>Overview of the functionality Patient must have a PHR app and have a valid PHR address Hospital must generate a HIP QR code and display it at the registration counter Patient scans the QR code from his phone camera or his PHR app If scanned from phone camera &amp;ndash; The list of installed PHR apps is shown on the phone. The user can select any of the apps if scanned from within the PHR app, the app will call the share-profile API on the HIE-CM The HIE-CM will verify this is a registered healthcare provider and call the share-profile api on the end of the HRP that is linked to this HIP The HRP software can create a screen to display all the scanned profiles and allow the operator to select them for fast registration include any images from the PHR app / EMRSBX for this feature</description></item><item><title>By scanning HIP QR code</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/shared-verbally/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/shared-verbally/</guid><description>Overview of the functionality Patient must have a valid PHR address Patient verbally shares the PHR address at the Health operator. OTP authentication will be required only if PHR address is shared verbally. include any images from the PHR app / EMRSBX for this feature
API Sequence S.No Collection &amp;amp; verification of ABHA by HIP APIs call on the Gateway APIs that are expected to be available at the HIP end by the Gateway 1.</description></item><item><title>By scanning PHR Address QR</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/scanning-phraddr-qr/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/scanning-phraddr-qr/</guid><description>Overview of the functionality Patient must have a PHR app or PHR card and have a valid PHR address Hospital must have a scanner available at the registration counter Hospital operator scans the QR code on patient PHR card or from PHR mobile App. After scanned HIP will call the share-profile API on the HIE-CM The HIE-CM will verify this is a registered healthcare provider and call the share-profile api on the end of the HRP that is linked to this HIP The HRP software can create a screen to display all the scanned profiles and allow the operator to select them for fast registration Then the detials like ABHA ID, PHR address,name,gender,sateId,districtId,dob,address will be shared with health facility include any images from the PHR app / EMRSBX for this feature</description></item><item><title>Discovery from PHR Apps</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/discovery-from-phrapp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/discovery-from-phrapp/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>