<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Collect &amp; Save PHR Address on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/index.html</link><description>Recent content in Collect &amp; Save PHR Address on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 17:53:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>By scanning HIP QR code</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/scanning-hip-qr2/index.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/scanning-hip-qr2/index.html</guid><description>Overview of the functionality Patient must have a PHR app and have a valid PHR address Hospital must generate a HIP QR code and display it at the registration counter Patient scans the QR code from his phone camera or his PHR app If scanned from phone camera &amp;ndash; The list of installed PHR apps is shown on the phone. The user can select any of the apps If scanned from within the PHR app, the app will call the share-profile API on the HIE-CM The HIE-CM will verify this is a registered healthcare provider and identify the HRP linked to this HIP in the ABDM registry The Gateway will call the share-profile api on the callback URL registered for this HRP The HRP software must create a screen to display all the scanned profiles for a (counter) code The operator (at a counter) should be able to select a shared profile and perform a fast user registration Remember to correctly handle this for both new and returning patients Create a QR code for your Health Facility Patient must have a PHR app and have a valid PHR address.</description></item><item><title>By scanning PHR Address QR</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/scanning-phraddr-qr/index.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/scanning-phraddr-qr/index.html</guid><description>Overview of the functionality Patient must have a PHR app with a valid PHR address or physical card like a ABHA card Hospital must have a 2D Barcode scanner available at the registration counter The HRP software registration page have text box to load data scanned from PHR QR Code. Hospital operator scans the QR code on patient PHR card or as displayed in PHR mobile App The Patient details like PHR address, Name, DOB, Gender, State Id, District Id, etc are embedded in the QR code as a JSON HRP software must validate the scanned data and collect a linking token from ABDM THe software must use the information scanned to register the patient and save the PHR Address Example QR Codes QR Codes in PHR Apps { &amp;#34;hidn&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;42-7175-8604-4553&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;phr&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;kiranma@sbx&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;name&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;Kiran Anandampillai&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;gender&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;M&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;statelgd&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;4&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;distlgd&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;44&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;dob&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;xx-9-19xx&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;address&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;As declared by the user&amp;#34; } Please note that &amp;ldquo;hidn&amp;rdquo; is available only if the PHR address has been linked with a ABHA</description></item><item><title>By sharing PHR Address verbally</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/shared-verbally/index.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/shared-verbally/index.html</guid><description>Overview of the functionality Patient must have a valid PHR address Patient verbally shares the PHR address to the health facility during registration Facility initiates a mobile OTP authentication for this PHR address Then patient will receive an OTP on their mobile which they must share with the operator The facility sends the OTP to the HIE-CM. On successful validations it gets the demographic details of the user and a new linking token The HRP software must store this access(linking) token in their system for the purpose of linking care contexts to the patient.</description></item><item><title>New vs Returning Patients</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/new-vs-returning-patients/index.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/new-vs-returning-patients/index.html</guid><description>Every health facility has to do deal with both new and returning patients. It is important that the capture and saving of a PHR address be offered to both new and returning patients by the HRP software
New Patients For New users, its is recommended that all the demographic information saved by the HRP is exactly the same as in the PHR Address profile shared by the user.
Returning Patients The following is the recommended steps to be followed by the HRP software</description></item></channel></rss>