<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Collect &amp; Save PHR Address on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/</link><description>Recent content in Collect &amp; Save PHR Address on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 17:53:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>By scanning HIP QR code</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/scanning-hip-qr2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/scanning-hip-qr2/</guid><description>Overview of the functionality &amp;laquo;&amp;laquo;&amp;laquo;&amp;lt; HEAD
Patient must have a PHR app and have a valid PHR address Hospital must generate a HIP QR code and display it at the registration counter Patient scans the QR code from his phone camera or his PHR app If scanned from phone camera &amp;ndash; The list of installed PHR apps is shown on the phone. The user can select any of the apps if scanned from within the PHR app, the app will call the share-profile API on the HIE-CM The HIE-CM will verify this is a registered healthcare provider and identify the HRP linked to this HIP in the ABDM registry The Gateway will call the share-profile api on the callback URL registered for this HRP The HRP software must create a screen to display all the scanned profiles for a (counter) code The operator (at a counter) should be able to select a shared profile and perform a fast user registration Remember to correctly handle this for both new and returning patients Create a QR code for your Health Facility =======</description></item><item><title>By scanning PHR Address QR</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/scanning-phraddr-qr/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/scanning-phraddr-qr/</guid><description>Overview of the functionality Patient must have a PHR app or PHR physical card and have a valid PHR address Hospital must have a 2D Barcode scanner available at the registration counter Hospital operator scans the QR code on patient PHR card or from PHR mobile App The Patient details like ABHA ID, ABHA address, Name, Gender, State Id, District Id, DOB, State Name, District Name, Mobile and Address are encoded in the QR Code After scanning the QR Code the details of the patient are shared in JSON format { &amp;#34;hidn&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;12-3456-7777-7777&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;hid&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;test@ndhm&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;name&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;gender&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;statelgd&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;7&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;distlgd&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;77&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;dob&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;1977&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;state name&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;DELHI&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;district_name&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;CENTRAL&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;mobile&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;+919999977777&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;address&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;&amp;#34; } The HRP software registration page have text box to load data scanned from PHR QR Code.</description></item><item><title>By sharing PHR verbally</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/shared-verbally/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/shared-verbally/</guid><description>Overview of the functionality Patient must have a valid PHR address Patient verbally shares the PHR address to the Health operator. Mobile OTP authentication will be done on sharing PHR address verbally. HIP will send the request to HIE-CM with patient mobile authentication mode and PHR address. Then patient will receive an OTP which is forwarded to the HIE-CM. The HIE-CM will validates the OTP and creates a new access token just for the purpose of linking.</description></item><item><title>Discovery from PHR Apps</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/discovery-from-phrapp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/save-phr-address/discovery-from-phrapp/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>