<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Creation of ABHA Number on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/abha-number/index.html</link><description>Recent content in Creation of ABHA Number on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 17:53:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/abha-number/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Using Aadhaar OTP</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/abha-number/aadhar-otp/index.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 09:30:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/abha-number/aadhar-otp/index.html</guid><description>Registration via Aadhaar OTP Applicable To HMIS / LMIS (PVT) Government Health App Using Aadhar OTP Mandatory Mandatory Functionality Overview ABHA Number can be created by authenticating with Aadhaar. Those who have their Aadhaar number linked with their mobile number can use this method to generate their ABHA no. Consent must be explained &amp;amp; collected from the user prior to performing Aadhaar OTP authentication. Once the user is successfully authenticated, the system will generate 14 digit ABHA number.</description></item><item><title>Using Aadhar Biometric</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/abha-number/aadhar-biometric/index.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 09:30:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/abha-number/aadhar-biometric/index.html</guid><description>Coming Soon.. Note To be documented after V3 APIs are released.
Applicable To HMIS / LMIS (PVT) Government Health App Using Aadhar Biometric Optional Mandatory Overview To enable beneficiary registration using Aadhaar Biometric, a client needs to have a Aadhaar Registered Device (RD Device) that allows capture and processing of Biometrics of the beneficiary. This RD Service returns an encrypted PID block containing signed biometrics (using device private key within the registered devices secure zone) back to the calling application.</description></item><item><title>Using Aadhar Demographic</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/abha-number/aadhar-demographic/index.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 09:30:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/abha-number/aadhar-demographic/index.html</guid><description>Using Aadhar Demographic Applicable To HMIS / LMIS (PVT) Government Health App Using Aadhar Demographic Not Applicable Mandatory Functional Overview Aadhaar Demographic authentication allows creation of a new ABHA number or retrieval of an existing ABHA number, given the Aadhaar number and Demographic details as per Aadhaar. This API is also useful for offline scenarios as the healthcare worker can capture the Aadhaar details when there is no connectivity and generate the ABHA number once connectivity is available.</description></item><item><title>Using Driving Licence</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/abha-number/driving-license/index.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 09:30:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/abha-number/driving-license/index.html</guid><description>ABHA Number Creation via Driving Licence Applicable To HMIS / LMIS (PVT) Government Health App Using Driving License Optional Optional Functionality Overview Currently ABDM supports Driving License (DL) for ABHA number generation, apart from Aadhaar.
The user is requested his/her mobile number to be linked with ABHA Number.
An OTP is sent to the given mobile number and after verifying the OTP , demographic information of the user is captured along with the driving license number .</description></item><item><title>Download ABHA Card</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/abha-number/download-abha-card/index.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 09:30:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/abha-number/download-abha-card/index.html</guid><description>Download ABHA Card Applicable To HMIS / LMIS (PVT) Government Health App Download ABHA Card Mandatory Mandatory Functionality Overview PHR Applications must display the ABHA QR code inside their apps. Users can show this QR Code at Health Facilities and have it scanned during registration.
During assisted enrolment for ABHA number, the user should be provided with a printed ABHA card that can be shown by the user for subsequent visits for rapid registration.</description></item><item><title>Default ABHA Address</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/abha-number/default-abha-address/index.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 01:30:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/abha-number/default-abha-address/index.html</guid><description>Default ABHA Address What is ABHA Address?
ABHA Address is an easy to remember username that enables a user to access their health records digitally and share their records with various healthcare providers. An ABHA address may look like ‘name@abdm’. It is required to sign up on ABHA Application
Every 14-digit ABHA number is automatically issued a default ABHA address on the ABDM HIE-CM, which looks like 14-digit@sbx or 14-digit@abdm.</description></item><item><title>Profile Update</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/abha-number/profile-update/index.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 01:30:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-milestone1/abha-number/profile-update/index.html</guid><description>Profile Update Applicable To HMIS / LMIS (PVT) Government Health App Using Aadhar Demographic Optional Optional If you want to do profile update for any user, you can do it by using their ABHA number, via:
ABHA Website, if you ABHA number was created on Production website. ABHA Sandbox, if you ABHA number was created on Sandbox environment. If you want to do it in your application, more information is documented under PHR Application section</description></item></channel></rss>