<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Registration for ABHA on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/8-abha-number/abha-id-registration/index.html</link><description>Recent content in Registration for ABHA on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 17:53:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/8-abha-number/abha-id-registration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ABHA ID Registration via Aadhaar</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/8-abha-number/abha-id-registration/registration-via-aadhaar/index.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/8-abha-number/abha-id-registration/registration-via-aadhaar/index.html</guid><description>Registration via Aadhaar Number Overview of the functionality User can register ABHA ID with their Aadhaar Number. To enable beneficiary registration using Aadhaar OTP, an integrator needs to generate an Aadhaar OTP, followed by OTP verification. Once the OTP is verified, the client is returned complete profile data along with ABHA (Health ID) Number. Note: Mobile Number can be linked/verify with ABHA via using API
API Sequence The sequence of APIs used via this method are shown in the diagram below.</description></item><item><title>ABHA ID Registration via Other Documents</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/8-abha-number/abha-id-registration/registration-via-other-documents/index.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/8-abha-number/abha-id-registration/registration-via-other-documents/index.html</guid><description>ABHA ID Registration via Other Documents Overview of the functionality Currently we support Driving License (DL) &amp;amp; PAN for ABHA number generation, apart from Aadhaar.
ABDM plans to roll out other ID documents as well to enable creation.
The same will be communicated and updated in the documentation as necessary.
However, the integration flow will remain as the DL/PAN flow.
To enable beneficiary registration using other documents, the user is requested his/her mobile number to be linked with ABHA (Health ID) Number.</description></item><item><title>Link/De-link of ABHA Address</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/8-abha-number/abha-id-registration/link-delink-abha-addr/index.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/8-abha-number/abha-id-registration/link-delink-abha-addr/index.html</guid><description>Link/De-link of ABHA Address Overview of the functionality ABDM has now segregated the identity layer from the consent layer, which will ensure that the ABHA Number (earlier known as Health ID) provides a strong identity to an individual whereas an ABHA Address (earlier known as PHR Address) enables an individual to share their health records with different healthcare providers and payers. ABHA number can be link/delink with the ABHA address. Below are the API used linking ABHA number with ABHA address.</description></item></channel></rss>