<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Creation of ABHA Address on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/5-building-a-phr-app/create-abha-address/index.html</link><description>Recent content in Creation of ABHA Address on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 05:53:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/5-building-a-phr-app/create-abha-address/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Using Mobile Number</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/5-building-a-phr-app/create-abha-address/mobile-no/index.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 09:30:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/5-building-a-phr-app/create-abha-address/mobile-no/index.html</guid><description>Using Mobile Number Applicable To HMIS / LMIS (PVT) Government Health App Using Mobile Number Optional Optional Functionality Overview Description: Individual enters mobile number/email ID, and it is validated via the added mode of validation
Create an ABHA address of the format abc@abdm via mobile number / email ID using self-declared profile information filled in by an individual, such as photo, name, date of birth, gender, address. Mobile number is entered in profile info, in case a user is registering through mobile number and email ID is entered in profile info, in case a user is registering through email ID.</description></item><item><title>Using ABHA Number</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/5-building-a-phr-app/create-abha-address/abha-no/index.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 09:30:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/5-building-a-phr-app/create-abha-address/abha-no/index.html</guid><description>Using ABHA Number Applicable To HMIS / LMIS (PVT) Government Health App Using ABHA Number Optional Optional Functionality Overview Description: Individual enters ABHA address (xyz@abdm), and it is validated depending on auth mode of validation such as mobile OTP/aadhar OTP/email OTP or Password to Login.
In this flow Individual is given an option of creating ‘ABHA address through ABHA (Number) via KYC document. Please note, the list of KYC documents may be revised from time to time.</description></item><item><title>Link/De-link ABHA Address</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/5-building-a-phr-app/create-abha-address/link-delink/index.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 09:30:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/5-building-a-phr-app/create-abha-address/link-delink/index.html</guid><description>Link and De-Link ABHA Address Functionality Overview ABDM has now segregated the identity layer from the consent layer, which will ensure that the ABHA Number (earlier known as Health ID) provides a strong identity to an individual whereas an ABHA Address (earlier known as PHR Address) enables an individual to share their health records with different healthcare providers and payers. ABHA number can be linked or de-linked with the ABHA address.</description></item></channel></rss>