<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Link Care Context on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</title>
    <link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/link-care-context/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Link Care Context on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 04:10:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/link-care-context/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>HIP Initiated linking</title>
      <link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/link-care-context/hip-initiated-linking/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 04:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/link-care-context/hip-initiated-linking/index.html</guid>
      <description>HIP Initiated linking Applicable when: User has come to the hospital &amp;amp; abha address has been captured during registration
  When a new health record is created for the patient, it needs to be linked to the ABHA address (HIP initiated linking)
  If linking token has expired, a new link token is obtained via demo auth &amp;amp; health record must be linked.
  Here&amp;rsquo;s more to understand on HIP initiated linking:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notification to Mobile</title>
      <link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/link-care-context/notification-mobile/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 04:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/link-care-context/notification-mobile/index.html</guid>
      <description>Notification to Mobile Applicable when: User has come to the hospital, does not share ABHA address during registration but shares mobile, name, age, gender.
  Health Information Provider (HIP) calls an API with just the mobile number to notify the user that a new health record has been created for the patient.
  HIPs can send SMS to patients in case they have not registered and do not have a health-ID after their visit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discovery &amp; link</title>
      <link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/link-care-context/discovery-link/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 04:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/link-care-context/discovery-link/index.html</guid>
      <description>Discovery &amp;amp; link Discovery of the patient’s information at the HIP   When the gateway calls an HIP system and requests for a particular patient’s records with a set of verifiable Ids, the process of information discovery begins.
  Upon receipt of the request, the HIP health repository reverts with a set of care context labels (in masked form).
  The following flow diagram details the flows that take place during patient information discovery from the HIP perspective:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>