<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Retrieve your ABHA account on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/retrieve-abha-account/</link><description>Recent content in Retrieve your ABHA account on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 17:53:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/retrieve-abha-account/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Retrieve ABHA via Aadhaar OTP</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/retrieve-abha-account/retrieve-abha-aadhaar-otp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/retrieve-abha-account/retrieve-abha-aadhaar-otp/</guid><description>Retrieve ABHA via Aadhaar OTP Overview of the functionality To retrieve ABHA (Health ID), an OTP is sent on a registered mobile number and the user&amp;rsquo;s health ID is retrieved from the ABDM server. The sequence of APIs used via this method is shown in the diagram below. API Sequence The sequence of APIs used via this method are shown in the diagram below.
API Information Request Response Generate Aadhaar OTP on Registered mobile number Explanation - API accepts Aadhaar Number and then generates OTP for linked number as part of Forgot flow.</description></item><item><title>Retrieve ABHA via Mobile OTP</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/retrieve-abha-account/retrieve-abha-mobile-otp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/6-m1-apis/retrieve-abha-account/retrieve-abha-mobile-otp/</guid><description>Retrieve ABHA via Mobile OTP Overview of the functionality To retrieve ABHA (Health ID), an OTP is sent on mobile number along with the user&amp;rsquo;s demographic detail. User&amp;rsquo;s health ID is retrieved from the ABDM server. API Sequence The sequence of APIs used via this method are shown in the diagram below.
API Information Request Response Generate Mobile OTP as part of Forgot flow Explanation - API accepts Mobile Number and then generates OTP for it.</description></item></channel></rss>