<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Notify or Link new records on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/7-sharing-health-records/notify-on-new-records/index.html</link><description>Recent content in Notify or Link new records on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 17:53:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/7-sharing-health-records/notify-on-new-records/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Notify via SMS</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/7-sharing-health-records/notify-on-new-records/notify-via-sms/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/7-sharing-health-records/notify-on-new-records/notify-via-sms/index.html</guid><description>Whenever a new Health record (Prescription, Lab Report, etc) is created by the HRP and is ready to be shared with the patient, the HRP must check if there is a saved PHR address available for the patient.
If there is no PHR address saved, the HRP must notify ABDM that there is now a new health record for the patient. The API only expects a mobile number. No information on the name of the patient or any details of the health record are part of the notification requirement.</description></item><item><title>Link a new record</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/7-sharing-health-records/notify-on-new-records/auto-link-withphr/index.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/7-sharing-health-records/notify-on-new-records/auto-link-withphr/index.html</guid><description>Overview of the functionality: Patient must have a valid PHR address Patient PHR address is already shared with HIP/HRP either during registration or discovery method A new health record is generated for this patient at the HRP The HRP checks if it has a valid linking token saved or obtains a new token via demographic auth The HRP decides if it will create a new care context for this health record or add to an existing care context If it is a new care context then the HRP links it with the PHR address If it is an existing care context, The HRP updates the existing care context Following is the API sequence diagram :</description></item></channel></rss>