<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Building a HRP on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/</link><description>Recent content in Building a HRP on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 17:53:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Support Discovery of Records</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/discovery-from-phrapp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/discovery-from-phrapp/</guid><description>Overview of the functionality User must have a PHR app and have a valid PHR address User is logged in into their PHR App User searches for a health facility which they have visited in the past. The health facility must be a HIP (part of facility registry) and linked with a HRP for discovery to be supported User makes a discovery request via PHR app - ie requests the HIP to find any health records in their name User shares details from their PHRAddress ie Name, Date of birth gender, verified mobile no with the HIP / HRP The HRP is expected to search its database for any records that match this patient.</description></item><item><title>Link Health Facilities with HRP</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/register_and_link_health_facility/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:00:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/2-sharing-health-records/register_and_link_health_facility/</guid><description>Register the health facility that uses your software and link it to your software endpoint Following article focuses on HMIS/LMIS/HRPs software providers can register the facilities which uses their softwares
All integrators are expected to first ensure their systems work correctly on sandbox before migrating to production.
On-boarding a Facility into a HFR: ABDM will support 2 methods to onboard health facilities
Method 1: Facility Manager registers via HFR Portal Health facility should sign up on the Health Facility Registry and then link the ABDM compatible HRP software it plans to use.</description></item></channel></rss>