<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Encryption &amp; Decryption on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/encryption-decryption/index.html</link><description>Recent content in Encryption &amp; Decryption on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 05:10:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/encryption-decryption/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Implementation Principles</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/encryption-decryption/implementation-principles/index.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 05:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/encryption-decryption/implementation-principles/index.html</guid><description>Encryption/Decryption Implementation Principles The following abbreviations are used in this section:
ECDH: Elliptic-curve Diffie–Hellman Key Exchange AES-GCM: Advanced Encryption Standard-Galois/Counter Mode DHK(U,P): Elliptic-curve Diffie–Hellman Key P and U (for Provider, and User) are annotations for the involved systems DHPK: Elliptic-curve Diffie–Hellman public key DHSK: Elliptic-curve Diffie–Hellman secret/private key RAND: Random String HKDF: Hash-based Key Derivation Function HIP: Health Information Provider HIU: Health Information User HDCM: Health Data Consent Manager Information shared as part of the data flow will be secured using an encryption mechanism that ensures perfect forward secrecy.</description></item><item><title>Fidelius CLI</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/encryption-decryption/fidelius-cli/index.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 05:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/encryption-decryption/fidelius-cli/index.html</guid><description>Fidelius CLI Fidelius CLI is an opinionated ECDH cryptography CLI tool (based on Curve25519, corresponding key-pair generation spec, custom HMAC-based Key Derivation Function for generating AES-GCM data encryption/decryption keys).
While Fidelius CLI can be used to serve a general purpose end-to-end encryption need, it has primarily been designed for encrypting/decrypting health data in the ABDM ecosystem (Ayushman Bharat Digital Mission — Indian Government&amp;rsquo;s venture at creating a digital backbone to support the integrated digital health infrastructure of the country).</description></item></channel></rss>