<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Encryption &amp; Decryption on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/encryption-decryption/index.html</link><description>Recent content in Encryption &amp; Decryption on ABDM Sandbox Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 05:10:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/encryption-decryption/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Implementation Guidelines</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/encryption-decryption/implementation-guidelines/index.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 05:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/encryption-decryption/implementation-guidelines/index.html</guid><description>Implementation Guidelines for Encrypting and Decrypting FHIR Data This guide outlines the technical foundations and protocols underpinning the process of encrypting and decrypting FHIR data within the ABDM ecosystem. Key actors in this system include Health Information Providers (HIPs), Health Information Users (HIUs), and Health Information Exchange Consent Managers (HIE-CMs).
Terminology In this guide, the following abbreviations are used:
HIP: Health Information Provider HIU: Health Information User HIE-CM: Health Information Exchange Consent Manager ECDH: Elliptic-curve Diffie–Hellman Key Exchange AES-GCM: Advanced Encryption Standard-Galois/Counter Mode P and U: Represent the Health Information Provider and Health Information User in the system, respectively DHPK: Elliptic-curve Diffie–Hellman Public Key DHSK: Elliptic-curve Diffie–Hellman Secret/Private Key RAND: Random String DHK(U,P): Elliptic-curve Diffie–Hellman Key / Shared Secret Key for a specific data exchange session between U and P HKDF: Hash-based Key Derivation Function SK(U,P): AES-GCM Encryption/Decryption Key for a specific data exchange session between U and P Security and Cryptographic Mechanism The FHIR data within this system is securely exchanged using a cryptographic mechanism ensuring perfect forward secrecy.</description></item><item><title>Fidelius CLI</title><link>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/encryption-decryption/fidelius-cli/index.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 05:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://kiranma72.github.io/abdm-docs/3-milestone2/encryption-decryption/fidelius-cli/index.html</guid><description>Fidelius CLI Fidelius CLI is a specialized command-line interface (CLI) tool designed for ECDH cryptography. It is based on Curve25519 and incorporates a custom HMAC-based Key Derivation Function, enabling the generation of AES-GCM keys for data encryption and decryption.
While Fidelius CLI can be used for various end-to-end encryption needs, its primary purpose is to secure health data within the ABDM ecosystem. ABDM stands for Ayushman Bharat Digital Mission, an initiative by the Indian Government to establish a nationwide digital infrastructure supporting integrated digital health services.</description></item></channel></rss>